The sun is shining.
It's a bright day outside.
But I don't give a shit about that.
Because I'm playing Noiter.
And I'm enjoying a nice IPA in this heat.
Because it is quite hot.
Okay, let me turn this shit off.
I love that changer.
I love that filter.
It's the best.
I'll never have spoken.
Oh man.
Welcome everybody.
How you doing?
Cheers.
Oh yeah.
Nothing like a cold beer on a hot day on a Sunday.
Just about to play some video games.
Man, I'm excited for Noiter.
Because I'm having a good run right now.
It's time.
A little past 3am where you're at.
Oh, okay.
It was like the complete opposite for you.
It's probably cold.
It's dark.
No beers.
Or maybe.
It's 5am there.
Oh damn.
Why are you up so early?
Or why are you up so late?
I guess.
Maybe you're like a night owl.
Or more like a moth, I would say, in your case, right?
Not so much an owl.
More like a moth.
Still a few hours until beer o'clock for you.
Okay, stranger.
What's up, Crowwater?
How's it going?
Engage in some heavy noitering.
Not to be confused with loitering.
That's different.
These are my objectives.
This is the map.
This is where I am.
I'm somewhere here.
I dug last time straight through a wall.
Straight through the densest rock the world has ever known.
And I emerged in the wizard's den.
Okay?
And there's stuff up there as well.
So very easily destroyable terrain here.
Oh, you can't see my mouse.
Right here, easily destroyable terrain.
And then down here we have the wizard's den.
And I intend to map the shit out of this place before I end up dying.
Because I will die.
Let's just be real here.
I already accept my inevitable death.
I just want to get as much ink on the parchment before I croak.
That's the plan.
I could start drinking at noon, but I'm trying not to.
Nobody judges anybody here.
Bro writes better with a mouse than I do by hand.
No, no, no, no.
I use a pen.
Don't worry about it.
I have a pen.
There's no way I can do that with a mouse.
That is a pen.
Trying to make a rain world map.
I guess so.
I guess the map in rain world was already there for me.
So I didn't need to make one there.
If you like making maps, you should play the DS Zelda games.
I do want to play some of the older Zelda games.
Because I've heard they're quite nice.
Also, I need to turn off the rain.
Because it is sunny outside.
What we really need is sun and wind.
That map looks cool.
You made it by playing through, I guess.
I did.
So this is almost everything I've explored.
There are certain places I've been that I just haven't filled out yet.
So I know there's an ancient laboratory up here, for example, that I haven't... because I don't know the dimensions of it yet.
I know there's like a cave here that's dark, that I also need to map properly.
And some other places too.
Like I know there's stuff right here that I need to look at.
But I'm slowly just... I'm trying to make it as accurate as possible.
That's why I don't immediately fill it out.
I need to get at least approximate proportions, you know?
But yes, thank you very much.
You missed last stream?
Oh man, you missed the biggest of things you don't even realize.
Immense things.
Things you wouldn't believe.
Sea beams glittering in the darkness of the Tenhauser Gate.
No, okay, Yujiri, I am in the middle of a really good run right now.
And I was in the vault.
And I dug through the wall.
And I emerged in some unknown place, which then turned out to be not so unknown.
Because it's let down to the Wizards then, where I have already been.
So I'm currently there and I want to explore everything there.
I want to basically get the outline of whatever region I'm in right now and map it.
And then take it from there.
Yeah, the Loki lair, man.
That shit scares me!
I don't like it.
In fact, it needs to cry as well.
Crying face.
So yeah, that's where I'm at.
Engage!
So you guys know the rules?
Alright, you know it by now.
I will jump in and enjoy this wonderful Sunday.
Also, sorry for not warning this stream ahead of time.
It just happened spontaneously.
So yeah, I apologize for that.
For the future Vought watchers, I apologize for not putting this in warning before I started.
But here it is.
I am gonna shut you guys down.
Hold on.
Let's see any last messages before you all get thrown away.
Have fun Oliver.
Thank you Frank.
Hope you get a big raid midstream.
Don't worry about it.
I'm just here to have fun.
Okay.
Are you guys ready?
I'm fucking ready.
It's time to hit the on switch.
And you have been shut down.
Okay.
Also, I'm recording perfectly.
Good.
No more 1080p for YouTube.
I feel so bad whenever I forget that.
Let's see.
All right.
Let's see here.
What was I doing?
Right.
I picked up this.
So this is the area I'm in and it goes down over here and it goes like, okay, let's just get the outline here.
The exact dimensions are a little mysterious to me.
So this is where I emerge.
Also, let me just...
That's my wand.
I have the digging.
I have a even better digging wand.
For the hard materials, I have a soft digger and a hard digger.
A soft dig and a hard dig.
Oh man.
I'm a child.
I am.
I'm not gonna deny it.
Where did I emerge from?
Hold on.
Where did I?
Must have been further up.
Still have no teleport, which is a bummer.
I emerged from... Oh man, I went... Holy shit.
All the way up here.
Wow.
There.
Okay.
So hold on.
Let me see here.
I basically made a path.
I'm just gonna assume I was halfway.
I don't exactly remember where I was there, but I dug this way and it sort of went... Hold on.
The layout, I guess... I'm assuming it links like that.
So there's like stuff here.
It's a little bit rugged.
I'm gonna make it rugged on purpose to make it look nice.
Let's say it's like there.
Okay.
Whoops.
I need a straight line.
Like this.
Okay.
That's the layout I think is happening right here.
Delete these two.
Okay.
Let's see how far up this goes.
This stuff is easily diggable.
Look at that.
Oh wait, I'm actually low on HP.
I should probably find some healing.
Okay.
I gotta find blood because I have vampirism and I have permanent shield, fire immunity, peace with gods, and that's right, extra perk.
I think I have one perk left to pick, but that's it.
That's all the perks I'm gonna get.
Hopefully it's gonna be a good one.
It sort of angles a little bit upwards here.
I
wonder if these mean anything.
That looks like the end boss, sort of.
With an arrow pointing up.
Glowing lands.
Oh, this goes up far.
What the hell?
Okay, there is an end.
Or is there?
No, there's not.
I'm hearing something.
Ah, look at you, little fucker.
What are you doing here?
Dude, this goes up really far.
Oh, I hear another one.
There he is.
Got him.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, what's happening?
Don't you shoot that shit at me.
What did you even come from?
Get rid of that lava.
Oh my god, there's so many of these.
I don't like there's lava flowing downwards now.
I bet I'm gonna die to that somehow later if I fall down into it.
Oh, hello.
Dude, this place is crawling with these dudes.
Oh wait, I'm also fire immune.
Forgot about that.
Oh, hello.
Yo, HP.
So much HP.
I'm not immune to lava though, pretty sure.
Oh my goodness.
The problem here is they bleed lava and not blood.
Actually, one of them bleed blood.
So if I can get rid of this lava.
Oh, I have no more water.
Shit.
Oh, it's too risky this.
Guys, I'm gonna play it ultra safe here.
This is the pussy play.
I don't care.
I'm going back to find blood and then I'm coming back in here.
I'm going all the... Oh, look at all this lava.
Yeah.
This is bad.
Oh wait, it's not actually being calculated.
It seems after a certain range.
Do you see that?
The lava was just sort of hanging out in the air.
I'm being pussy.
I'm going back to a place that is less dangerous to find some blood.
We gotta heal.
I can also use this opportunity to just clean up this tunnel a little bit.
Because it's kind of rugged, isn't it?
Not the prettiest thing.
Wish I had a teleport one right now.
Man, I ducked for a long time.
Okay, not that long.
Okay, we got water.
I need that.
Beautiful.
Just grab all the essentials here.
Good.
What was on this?
Rocks.
There's blood.
Drink it.
Oops.
No, no, no, don't spray it.
Concentrated mana.
Fuck off.
I love hortas.
They're like blood bags.
Eat, eat, eat.
Oh yeah.
Look at all that healing.
Okay, good start.
I'll turn all this to water.
I am not toxic immune.
Oh, hello.
I need to find a big bath of blood.
There electricity down there.
Oh, look at that.
Oh, and there's blood too.
This is perfect.
Oh, lovely.
No, don't you fucking.
It corroded all the blood.
I need a piece of shit.
I was about to feast.
Maybe it's time to throw this away.
I'm not feeling it.
I am feeling this though.
Inviseble you?
And you know what?
Yeah, invisible me place.
We have been here before.
You know what?
Yeah, let's just keep exploring this place a little bit more.
May as well do that.
Get a little bit stronger, find some more hearts, and then we head to the east.
To the Wizards Den.
And we explore that place.
I don't know why I was so surprised to find Wizards there.
This is called Wizards Den.
Makes total sense.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Oh, the blood is real.
Just no acid people right now, please.
Okay.
You.
Nice.
Look at all this blood.
This is exactly what I needed.
Holy shit.
In fact, give me more.
I don't think I've ever seen this much blood before in this game.
This is just amazing.
Damn, it's overflowing.
And there's even more now because I'm killing these guys.
Okay, we cannot let this get the decontaminated.
This bloodbath needs to stay pristine.
Oh, yeah.
No, no, no, pristine, pristine.
Shit.
It's okay, it's okay.
Get some more blood.
Nice.
Yeah, you know what?
I'm just gonna explore this area fully, get all the hearts that I can, heal up all that stuff.
And then we go back to the Wizards Den.
Because I want to be extremely prepared for the unknown.
And that place is scary to me.
Oh, the snot.
These guys multiplying?
What's happening here?
I'm getting way more blood than I asked for, but I'm happy about it.
We also have to remember, I have a perk that will give me more HP.
That I still haven't grabbed yet.
And I'm saving it until I have even more maximum HP.
Because then the effect will be greater.
And I know it's greedy.
I'm a greedy boy.
But imagine, imagine the possibilities.
Got him?
Thank you.
Is that leaking?
What is that leaking?
What is that?
Is that whiskey?
Wait, is that moonshine?
I think it is.
It was leaking whiskey.
That's what's also causing all this.
Cool.
These guys are making the Schrader, bro.
Oh, a sniper!
Didn't even see you there.
And I can go anywhere because I have a laser cutter, baby.
And the wand.
What might you be?
Man, they just keep coming.
One after each other.
Whoa!
Digging blast!
Hold on.
It costs zero mana drain.
Damage drill three.
Wait, this one does more?
Huh.
Um, I am a little curious here.
I'm gonna take that back to the lab.
I'm gonna do that right now.
I gotta see the difference.
There's gotta be something else to it.
Back to the lab again.
Hold on, I can test damage on the statue.
Oh, but it's kind of bugged, right?
I wonder if it's the same with a digging blast.
Let's see.
I think so.
Let me just use this only.
You're gonna... Wow, it only does three damage.
It says more powerful digging, but the damage is lower.
So I think this is actually better to have this here and then use this as a digging, you know?
Also, how's this wand?
It's not that great.
Uh, let's leave some of these here.
A bunch of digging blasts.
In fact, I'll take one of them and have up here.
The double can also stay here.
This wand, it has a lot of slots, granted.
Oh, we also have this stuff.
Sparkbolt with double trigger.
Double trigger.
Ooh, hold on.
Oh, we also have the plasma enhancer.
We gotta do that here.
Enhance the shit out of that.
What does this do?
Let me see the difference.
Oh, it's way better!
Dude.
And because, look at this, it's sparkbolt with double trigger.
So it casts two new spells upon collision.
The first spell of which is just that one.
But if we do a double now...
Uh, wait, no.
Put it here.
If I now add this as well.
Wait, let me think.
Double trigger.
So it's gonna...
Oh, no, wait.
It only shoots this one at once.
But I want all of these effects to be applied to both of these, right?
Oh, this one is only being applied there, so I need to do that, I guess.
Oh, wait, that's even worse, I think.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
How did I have it?
What's about this?
It's hard to say.
I think this may be better.
Let me see the board.
It does shoot both of them.
This has got to do way more damage, right?
I could even do, instead of having a digging blast, I could probably put a spell in there, like an actual damage spell.
Maybe something like that, even.
Hold on.
Let's just experiment here.
Also, this wand is not bad either.
Not a bad wand.
Hold on.
Get this out of my way.
All right, let's have a sip.
Cheers, everybody.
Happy Sunday.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
So, what I want to do is... maybe that.
Let's see how much damage that does.
Well, I guess the damage is unreliable on this thing.
Yeah,
I mean, the damage does way more than it suggests here, by the way.
Because for some reason, it's not showing this, remember?
Which is like the whole thing.
It's like the important thing here.
Also, let
me see this again.
Yeah, I think this is better.
It does feel a little slower, though, somehow.
But it may just be because of this explosion sound.
I think I like this.
Let's try it.
Let's just roll with it.
If it feels worse, we're gonna switch it back.
I also want to make it one just with the circle of vigor, obviously.
But we got to pick up the wand we left behind.
And I'm gonna try, instead of having the...
Oh, what's it called?
The energy sphere.
I'm gonna try with the digging blast on it instead.
So that one, it's pretty dope like that, actually.
But with a digging blast, it can be even better because that costs how much mana?
You guessed it!
Zero.
Let's see.
Wait.
Oh, oh.
Oh, that sucks.
It's using... it goes oom because of this now.
Hold on.
Oh, that's bad.
Oh, that's annoying.
It's too good.
It's too fast.
I need to slow it down somehow.
I mean, this one also goes oom, I guess.
So, I mean, not really a big difference.
Right.
Unless I can use a better wand with it.
Let me see.
What does this have?
It has 360 and charge speed 108.
So what I need is a small cast delay.
Small recharge.
Yeah, I basically need good stats.
That one's bad.
That one is maybe just as good.
Let's see here.
If not better.
Okay, it's a little bit too slow.
And that is because the recharge time is much higher, isn't it?
That's why.
No, and also the cast delay, I guess.
This does reduce cast delay, but not enough.
So when I use this right now, I'm limited by, I think, cast delay.
Do we have anything that can reduce cast delay?
This adds a lot.
Flowing lands, nah.
Unless I simply throw on a shit ton of these and call it a day.
Something like this.
Okay, so it's cast delay right now is the issue.
So if I do a double
there with that, it's got to be just a little bit better, I guess.
I just wonder how good digging that is.
I don't think I'm impressed.
Oh, we also have this wand.
This one can stay here.
Yeah.
Honestly, I'm just gonna switch this back to what I had before.
Let's put these here at least.
Yes.
That is the wand.
Put this here.
Put that there.
Why do I have two of these plasma cutters?
I just need one of them.
There.
Oh wait, this one.
Oh wait, did I just fuck up?
Hold on.
What did I have on here?
This is my digging.
I'm gonna use this.
I'm gonna try the digging blast to see how that goes.
And then I have this digger and then this guy can be something.
Maybe that.
Maybe that's just a healing.
Could be nice to just have, you know?
Like, I think it's nice to have emergency healing.
I'm taking it.
Like, if we're in a bad spot and we need to heal immediately, it's nice to have.
The vampirism stuff is like for in-between fights, obviously.
Mostly.
Here we go.
And I'm also gonna try this new setup I have going there.
See how much damage I do now.
It's exciting.
A little bit more chaotic, I guess, because it shoots things off in every direction.
Uh-oh, we got an Ukuskibi, I think.
I could fuck that up.
Hold on.
After digging.
Okay, that wasn't bad.
The digging is... I want to say it's not as good, honestly, here.
Also, it's that one.
Go.
Am I slippery?
I am.
Hold on.
I need to be on slippery for this.
There we go.
I cannot be slipping right now.
Out!
Oh, nice.
Okay, there's still electricity.
Oh, there's a heart in there!
All right, I need to get it.
This is gonna be a bit of a difficult mission.
Nah, it's easy.
That's... Oh, it is actually electrified.
Oh, I see the box.
I see the box.
Let's go mess it up.
Lovely!
Danger.
Oh, that's more!
I like my energy orb more.
I'm gonna get it.
I can't, I can't do this.
The energy orb is my bay.
The digging blast is kind of shit.
I mean, because I run out of mana.
Oh, that looked really good.
Go.
That looked amazing.
I think I'm doing way more damage.
It feels better so far.
Uh, replace this back place.
Oh, yeah.
Energy sphere, my beloved.
We are back.
It just has a larger digging radius as well, you know?
Uh, hold on.
Is it actually better?
Okay, it may not be better, actually.
But it feels better.
I can also dig at a distance, right?
So.
I just need a good wand.
That's all I need.
Oh, my god.
The damage is surreal.
Oh, hello.
Oh, yeah, I do way more damage like this.
Guys, I made the sickest wand ever.
Oh, I'm so happy.
I just keep improving on my design.
It has become perfected at this point.
Look, there's more electricity going on there.
We don't like that.
Blow it.
Oh, yeah, they instantly die.
This thing was a death trap, man.
Holy crap.
I'm gonna kill these guys.
Are they gonna burn?
What's up, fools?
Come on now.
Whoa!
Where all these guys come from?
Oh, yeah, this one feels incredible.
This may be one of the best ones I've ever made.
Oh, hello there.
Oh, yeah, insta-kill these guys as well.
It's just so good.
We gotta take care of that hazard.
Come on, asset.
Eat through the stuff.
Yeah, that's fine.
What is that?
Oh, it's freezing vapor.
Uh-oh.
Wait, what is in here?
Rusted steel.
No, it's blood.
I don't know why it said that.
Give me some more hearts.
Oh, I hear electricity.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
There we go.
There you are.
I'm still deathly afraid of those guys, because if they can catch me in like a stunlock with the electricity, then I'm really scared.
That stuff is terrifying.
Let's see what's on this wand.
I predict black hole.
What's that?
True orbit.
Makes a projectile rotate around the caster like an orbiting planet.
Magic arrow with trigger.
Oh, that's 35 mana drain.
That's a lot.
I am curious about this one, guys.
I think this one could be really sick if we find the healing bolt, or whatever it's called.
Depends how big of a radius this orbit is, right?
But for now, I'm going to leave it here.
But that is very intriguing.
Whoa!
Uh, sniper?
Where are thou?
Another wand.
Dude, this increased girth on the laser is actually very nice.
Now that looks like a good wand, doesn't it?
0.22 castelay?
0.52, and this reduces castelay by 0.33.
So, oh, but it's not gonna be as good as this, because basically what I want out of a digging wand, and this is something I've realized now, I want the castelay and recharge time to be close to zero on both.
That is what a good digging wand is, right?
We want to be able to do things quick and have enough mana for it, too.
So this is not quite there, but if I can find another reduced recharge time and add mana, then I'm golden.
That is not a bad wand, though.
It may even be... nah, nah, nah.
Let's leave it there for now.
Invisiblium.
Throw that up.
Become invisible.
Oh!
Dude, my shield blocks that, too!
That's nice.
I'm out of blood.
May have to go back to the blood repository.
Yeah, we're playing this safe.
We gotta have a full flask of blood at all times.
May just take a shortcut.
Let's try and dig.
I've become a fan of just digging.
Just digging.
Nothing else.
Oh, look at that.
Yo, the good news about this laser cutter right now is that the width of the actual laser is big enough to allow me to walk through.
So it's like the perfectly sized, you know?
It's gonna make it much easier to dig through things later.
Or, I mean, I'm gonna save a lot of time.
Random damage.
Shuffle.
This is actually a good digging wand.
These two together, it doesn't matter in which direction...
actually does the matter.
But it reduces recharge time.
This may be better with this.
I'm gonna leave it here again.
I may just come back for these.
I just don't want to go back to the home base already.
I want to explore a bit more before I go.
What?
I was a bit too close.
Jesus.
I thought I was at a safe distance.
I was wrong.
Oh,
hello.
Blood.
That is what I need.
You know what?
Fill up the water first.
There we go.
And now we fill up the blood.
Can we get rid of this?
Thank you.
How am I not bursting at the seams with all this blood in my system?
All right.
Good.
I want to get just a bit more though.
I know there's some blood over here.
Somewhere.
Where was it?
This was not here.
I haven't discovered this.
There it is.
This guy's stuck in there.
Look.
Got him.
Just a bit more.
Nice.
We're back on track.
All I need right now is explosion immunity and I'm golden.
Imagine that.
I've had explosion and fire immunity together before and it was crazy.
Let's get to a safe distance.
I hate
these things.
Hello.
Why are you bleeding lava though?
Aren't you throwing freezing things?
I want to kill this.
Grab that one.
That one.
Next.
I'm so ready.
None of these guys have anything on me.
Look at this.
Show me the hearts.
I really need to explore every square inch because they could be like in a little corner like that.
You know, in a little pocket.
I'm gonna be on the lookout for it.
What's in here?
Anyone else?
I think my audio is starting to lag a little bit.
It's a bad sign.
May need to restart the game.
Oh, and people did say I need to click a restart with mods or something.
Actually, let's try that right now.
Mods?
No.
Wait.
Mods settings.
Okay guys, how do I restart with mods?
You guys told me it was quicker.
I'm gonna look at chat in a second.
Do you know?
Okay, I'm looking.
Mods.
Okay.
Mods restart with mods.
Thanks.
Restart.
Wait.
What enabled mods?
Do I have mods on?
No.
Oh wait, finished translation?
No, we want to keep it finished though.
Restart with enabled mods active, right?
I'm not like enabling mods like this, right?
Okay.
There we go.
Thanks guys.
Okay.
Nice.
Oh, that was quick.
That was really nice.
I gotta start doing that.
Yeah, that's a pro tip.
I think we're good to go.
Back to where we were.
I've checked that wand already.
That guy looks like he wants to give me a high five.
Hold it.
What is in the way?
I hate these little pixels of material that block my path.
Singular pixels.
Oh, watch this.
Bam.
Order there.
Order here.
Okay.
This is where I was before.
Wouldn't mind some electricity immunity.
Oh, that's the one I already checked.
Whoa.
Why did I take damage?
Oh, free.
Oh, freezing liquid.
I've never seen that.
At least I don't think I have.
I'm so happy.
I have peace with gods.
I can't even tell you how happy that makes me.
It may even be better.
It may actually be the best perk of all time.
Maybe even better than tinker with wands everywhere.
What's happening there?
Oh, it was just a lamp.
I thought it was an Ukuskivi embedded in the rock or something.
It's very narrow.
Ooh, look at that.
Lovely.
Thank you.
Oh, mix it up.
That's a bomb.
Let's get to safe distance.
Actually, let me blow this up first.
Now go over here and we blow that up.
Oh, yeah.
Contains a bunch of acid.
Bring some blood.
Stay topped up.
You lost your head, man?
Another crazy wand.
Those are some really good stats.
Well, these are at least.
I don't know about the Casterly and recharge.
It's like, yeah, it's OK.
But I want that that uber wand, you know, that amazing wand.
Oh, shit.
Hold up.
How exactly?
Right.
OK, so that's actually what I expected.
Yes.
Makes sense.
Um, guys, how well do you take to my new wand?
You want to maybe.
Oh, shit, they're coming through here now.
Come on.
No, change your mind.
Am I damaging them?
Guys, come on now.
Wait, what's that?
They're not taking damage.
Wait, they are taking damage.
Oh, yeah.
OK, OK, OK.
They just have a lot of HP.
As shit, but it's way faster than earlier.
Remember last time?
Goddamn.
Can I just get rid of this slime, please?
Can I dissolve slime?
Fuck, yeah.
Lovely.
Do I explore this place?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, wait.
We don't go in here without the teleport wand because of the clouds.
The clouds are just the worst.
Oil crap.
So many explosives, man.
Oh, look at all this.
It's going to become water.
All of it.
Oh, look how fast that reaction happened.
That is insane.
Get some water here.
Let's go.
I need some more blood now.
Did I see you there?
I did.
What's happening in here?
What is that?
Hold on.
Oh, never mind.
I thought it was something really special.
Dude, this place has been cleared of any dangers.
Just getting rid of all the explosives and stuff.
Oh, shit, we got a loose propane tank.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's what I'm talking about, baby.
Black holes and four of them.
I'm taking those back to the lab immediately.
Just kind of remember our way back.
Take it easy, kill the enemies.
Got a laser thingy.
Got it.
Wait, what's making electricity?
I hear bombs.
Oh, there you are.
It was you.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Whoops.
Wrong wand.
I'm used to having my digging wand on that.
Didn't mean to throw that.
Oh, I just had a sharp headache and now it's gone.
That was weird.
It happened in like one second.
Now it's gone.
What the fuck?
That's kind of worrying.
Take this.
Get the blood.
Nice.
Full HP.
It's a huge vat.
All right.
I need to go back to base.
Let me just remember where this wand was.
It was... Wait, where was it?
There.
Okay.
So I go up to the right.
Just go up.
In fact, just go all the way up and then to the right.
Follow the top, right?
That's the easiest way to do this.
I could just dig through here.
Nothing stops me.
I have peace.
The gods are on my side.
Yeah.
Just continue up here.
Oh my god.
It's so effective.
Right.
That was that one.
Okay.
I'm going to make a path here.
Sweet.
Damn right.
You look, you don't have to give me that message.
Can we just not have those messages appear because they scared the shit out of me.
I hate those messages.
I don't want this.
Let's get rid of the stuff I definitely don't want.
Ah, I don't know.
Okay.
The blood cloud.
It's nice in theory.
Actually, it is super nice.
But I just, I guess I will, I will need to use it somewhere so I can always come back and just get the blood.
Right.
But I don't want to have it on an active wand.
It feels like a waste of a slot for that.
Eldritch portal.
Fuck it.
Another one of these fuckers.
Put this here.
Okay.
Now the wand itself is actually not terrible.
I mean, it does have a very low mana charge speed, but it has super low cast delay, but recharge time is big.
So this is going to be super slow.
So if I can reduce that, I really don't want to, if I remove this up here, is this going to affect the wand?
Wait,
am I crazy or is this suddenly faster?
What?
Hold on.
Why the?
All right.
Well, I'm not going to question it.
Okay.
It's just as fast, isn't it?
No, not there, not there.
Is it, is it faster?
I think it's exactly the same.
So if I do this now, look at that.
Smooth as butter.
What if we do a triple on this and then we go a little nuts because they cost zero mana.
We triple it.
The ultimate digging.
Ooh.
Oh, that actually does cost some mana somehow.
Oh, because the triple spell.
Oh, that's the one draining mana.
Interesting.
This one drains no mana.
Wow.
And this is working just as fine.
Look at that.
Wait, why does that still?
Oh, the heavy spread costs mana too.
But I guess it's a little slower.
Look at that.
We're not going to run out of.
No, no, no.
That is totally enough.
That's beautiful.
I feel like this has become sort of a freak of a wand.
At this point, I'm not even sure I understand why it works the way it works.
Let me put this back.
No, it's exactly the same.
It feels like it at least.
Now we got to do that.
Circle of vigor.
Keep that there.
Yeah, I like it.
Although I'm going to keep this here because I want to go back and grab the reduce recharge time that I had on the other wand.
Yep.
Seems good.
Let's go.
I guess I'll notice if this wand is somehow worse now.
This feels a little slower, doesn't it?
Maybe I'm just imagining.
It's probably placebo.
If only I could see the proper DPS on the training dummy.
No, no, no.
Keep going left up here and then go down when I reach a certain point, I remember.
Actually, there was this.
Was it here?
It wasn't too far down.
It was not there.
Oh, you need to die immediately.
There we go.
Let's see the digging in action.
Oh, it's good.
It's good.
It's good digging.
It's just that I can't get through steel.
Best to be expected.
Like, look at this.
Oh, wow.
That's smooth as butter.
Really nice.
Oh, okay.
Now we're here.
So we go down.
Here, I guess.
No, that's not where the wand was.
Where the fuck was it?
Yeah, I have no clue where that wand is.
I guess we're just gonna have to walk around and hopefully find it.
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
That has to be the wand.
Yes, good.
Put it back here.
And now we move.
Awesome.
What's happening there?
You're my friend?
Why are you my friend?
At some point, he's not gonna be my friend anymore, and then I need to kill him.
See ya.
Careful now.
Electricity is scary.
Go slow.
I'm constantly on the lookout for electrified metals in the distance.
Shit.
Why is he on my side?
I don't get it.
Okay, electrified.
Be careful.
Let's see where the issue is.
There it is.
We found the cause of the problem.
Got it.
But there's more, I think.
Yeah, there's another one.
Ooh, that's so scary.
It's somewhere up on the top right, it seems.
Where are you?
There we go.
Nice.
There's another one.
This is exactly like that other place we were at.
Well, there's a chest in there.
The chest is now destroyed.
There was gold inside.
It is... I guess it's down there somewhere.
Shit, shit, shit.
Water, water, water, water, water.
Let's make a little hole out here.
Okay.
Yeah, there it is.
Dangerous eliminated.
Fantastic.
It's kind of fun taking out those things.
Identifying where they are, you know, and weeding out or rooting out the problem.
I don't know how to say that.
There's an expression for that.
But I totally butchered that.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Gotta get some water.
Stupid pixels.
Okay, check that one before.
We have emergency healing if we need it.
Get some more water.
Leave that water there, actually.
It's nice to have.
Oh, no, the Lukey layer.
I'm tempted to explore it.
Just because I feel like the rewards would be great, right?
I mean, I can go slow, I guess.
Let's go a little slow.
It's just super dark in here.
Oh, shit.
The music is creeping me out.
Oh, no, here we go.
Here we go.
This is what I feared.
Yep.
Like, I hate these things so much.
Where are you?
Okay, he needs line of sight to me, it seems.
Got him.
The audio is bugging.
Oh, God, kill it quick.
Oh,
please die.
The hell?
How the fuck are you not dead?
What is this?
Oh, my God, it's healing at the same time.
Somehow.
I hate this.
I killed him before.
I must have changed something about my wand that I don't understand this at all.
Oh, fuck me.
All right, all right, all right.
We gotta change our wand back to whatever the fuck it was before.
Oh, man.
I hate that.
Somehow they're healing and I don't understand why.
Like, I'm damaging them, but they're also healing at the same time.
Get fucking...
Remove those pixels.
There we go.
Okay.
Uh, what did I have before?
I guess I didn't have that one.
Or did I?
That one was not there.
And I guess this one wasn't there either.
Let's just check.
Eliminate one variable at a time here.
I'm tempted to eliminate multiple, but that's a bad idea.
Now, where are you, fucker?
I'm guessing you're close because of the music.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, here we go, here we go.
Okay, it's not healing.
It is healing, never mind.
Is it enough, though?
Why are you healing?
Fuck.
It must have been the double spark then.
Back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back.
So, I guess the issue is not this one, it's this one.
Where's my old spark?
Fuck, where is it?
What?
Did I leave it on a... I did.
Put it here.
Still take one of these, though.
Now, I'll throw this away.
Take that one back.
Put this one in.
Is that what's doing it?
Wait, oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is somehow bad now.
Get rid of that one.
Okay, let's see now.
Come on.
I definitely killed him with this wand.
All right, sir, can be small asshole.
Please fuck off while I'm dealing with a spider.
Are you healing?
It's still healing.
Oh, but I... now I'm damaged?
No, I...
I guess I damaged more than I healed now for some reason.
Huh.
What is happening?
I'm not gonna fucking question it.
I'm just gonna rock with this wand now, I guess.
Well, it's something to do with the double spark.
What does the double spark do?
So, the thing about this one, it has damage explosive.
Maybe that's... maybe explosive damage on those guys?
Heal them.
Which is kind of weird, but sure, could be the... could be the case, I guess.
But it's still healing now.
Do I have any explosive on this?
No.
Hmm.
Maybe it's just projectile damage that heals it.
And I had more projectile damage before.
And this one is... I guess it is a projectile, but it does say damage drill.
So maybe that's the difference.
All right, let's go back.
Now we know we can kill them.
I want melee immunity, man.
For these guys?
Oh yeah.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, but the clouds are in here.
Not... we... we gotta... we gotta... I gotta map this place anyway.
Just go slow.
As soon as I see a cloud, shoot it.
You know what would be amazing in here?
Invisible.
Invisibility.
Okay, that's not bad.
I got it.
I do seem to deflect it with my shield as well, if they get close.
That's nice.
Spider.
How fast can I kill you?
Look, it's still healing.
Okay, it's not bad.
It's not bad.
Jesus!
Ah!
Holy physics!
Shit!
Oh god, stop with the physics!
Dig!
Oh man, this thing is going nuts down there.
You know what?
How do you feel about this?
Kill it!
Got it!
Okay, that's not bad.
That's decently fast.
All this fucking slime!
Okay, this better be the reward I'm looking for.
Slime mist?
I hate it.
This is not the reward I was promised for the risk.
Also, I still have healing.
I don't!
We left emergency healing at home.
Shit.
Got him!
Okay, so they have like a small window where they turn into something that can be hit.
As long as you don't panic.
Oh, look at this now!
Very low castile.
But a recharge time of 0.7, so if we can eliminate that, that would be dope.
I may just grab it.
Should I just take it?
Ah, man.
Yeah, take it.
A lot of energy orbs.
We can encourage electricity.
Wait a minute.
Isn't that just... Oh, shit.
Got it!
Go!
Okay.
Oh,
I didn't want to do that.
Switch back, switch back.
Let's see.
That's so many wands in here, actually.
Dude, these wands are actually dope.
An extremely concentrated point of light that explodes after a moment.
This is not a bad wand.
It may even be better than this, just because of the low recharge compared to it.
And it's faster with mana charge and mana max and more slots.
I'm taking it.
This could become a nice digging wand.
Although, I mean, I already made a nice digging wand, didn't I?
But I guess I can make something else out of it.
0.17, 0.5.
Oh, but this mana charge speed up here is actually carrying me hard with that wand.
That's the big, nice thing about that, isn't it?
I like it, though.
Let's take it slow.
I need to look at the bright side here.
If I get rid of all the spiders in here, there's gonna be no more spiders!
Hey!
Right?
Logic!
And when there's no more spiders, there's nothing to be afraid of.
So just one by one, I need to cleanse this place.
And I can't tell where I've been because everything is dark in here.
I
see a chest, though.
Is that acceleration?
Um, why not?
Yeah, just drink a bunch of this until we find some blood.
Seems good, right?
That way we can run from the spiders.
Something's happening.
Oh!
Oh no, it's one of these things.
Penetrate the shields.
Got it.
Okay, we're at the top now.
We're gonna drain this.
Can we even?
Hold on, what's in the chest?
Extra Max HP!
Yo!
Look at this!
I can mouse over it, too.
I don't need to actually see it.
It's kind of neat.
Ah!
Yo!
There we go, there we go.
Get it out of there.
And then we need to do this.
Whee!
Drain, drain, drain, drain, drain, drain for me.
There we go, slowly but surely.
Look at that beautiful heart being revealed.
Now I'm gonna grab that without touching this crap.
Ah, nice.
Nice.
The thing about this digging bolt, or digging blast, it digs through the lush ground.
And the energy sphere did not do that.
So the roof is here.
And wait, what?
It makes sense!
We're back in the underground jungle!
Look at this!
Cool!
Very cool.
So it always connects, I guess.
That's good to know.
It means my map is right.
And slowly but surely all the spiders are being eradicated.
Oh, hello!
Nice.
We gotta make an escape route here.
We can't be stuck in the slime on the way out if someone comes running after us.
Come on, get rid of this.
Oh man, this is just nasty.
Nasty!
Nasty business, that.
Get rid of all this slime.
This is a mess.
Look at this shit, man.
Oh, we dug to here and then stopped.
Oh, that's cool.
I thought there was a whole cave up there somehow.
Don't drown.
Imagine drowning in spider blood.
Wouldn't that just be the worst?
It looks like we have a spider digging here.
And then it stopped.
I can't get through dense rock with this though, but I can use my laser cutter if I need to.
I'm not gonna though.
Not right now.
Oh.
Shit!
I was slow to react.
Got it!
Oh man, it's taking a lot of my HP!
I'm poison now.
We gotta go back.
It's too risky.
Low HP?
No, no, no, no, no.
We're playing it safe.
And there's no blood to be had in here, other than spider blood.
And that's not something we want to have.
You know, I could just go in here, I guess, for a bit.
Why not?
We could explore the jungle a bit more, since we're here.
Maybe we'll find some hearts, find some blood, and it's a nice, quiet, relaxing place.
It's not too dangerous.
Uh-oh.
Gotcha.
I'm poisoned again now.
What is that sound up here?
Boo!
What the fuck's happening here?
Okay, there's some blood down there.
Eat, eat, eat.
Drink, drink, drink.
Oh yeah, I remember this.
Dude, the digging... this is actually the fastest digging one I've ever made.
Just look at this.
Like, it has no hesitation to dig through soft materials.
It is insane.
Blood
for me.
What's this?
Oh.
Oh, nice blood.
Oh, you know what I want to do, guys?
We're gonna dig again on the wall, see if we can't get back to the right from here.
I'm gonna make small, like, tunnels everywhere.
We're gonna strip mine this fucking world.
What's down here?
Oh, nice.
Another portal.
I've been there.
Let me get that blood.
That's sweet, sweet blood.
Can I drink something I shouldn't have?
I drank poison!
Imagine if I didn't discover the blood in the flask technique.
I was eating that shit off the ground for ages.
Until I finally discovered that you didn't have to do that.
Uh, I remember seeing this one before.
Hold on.
Get rid of the poison.
No, I don't like the fact that it cast this weird spell.
Yes!
Cheers, everybody.
Lovely.
Here's a place we haven't been.
I think this is the same run where I discovered the worm technique of fighting.
I killed a bunch of, uh, stewards before I made peace with them.
Oh, yeah, there's that one.
I see not a bad wand.
It's a, it's a decent wand.
Like, why didn't I take that wand back then?
That's an okay wand.
Get some blood.
There we go.
So is this one.
This is also a decent wand.
Oh, here's the edge.
Oh, fuck.
I lost a lot of HP just now.
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We got the dragon cave here.
I don't think I ever did this.
Yeah, we never did this.
I was too weak.
I was too afraid.
No more, bitch.
I'm not afraid anymore.
Am I though?
Maybe I'm a bit afraid.
Nah.
We're okay.
I just gotta be ready to get the fuck out of here.
Suddenly, this guy pops out.
There we go.
We lose his HP quick.
Yeah, that, there we go.
There we go, baby.
And look at all the blood coming out of it too.
That's lovely.
Heavy spread.
Uh, damage field.
Give, gives a projectile an energy field that constantly deals 3.5 damage to nearby creatures.
Huh.
Personal lightning caster.
I don't know.
I don't know about this.
Three spells per cast.
Not a big fan of that.
This one does seem interesting.
I gotta be honest.
That one does seem interesting.
I think it could be really nice if you add some extra damage to it.
Oh wait, this is a modifier though.
Depends how often that damage is applied, I guess.
Let's just grab all this blood.
Sawblade orbit.
I have that already.
You hear that?
The fuck is that?
There's something there.
Someone's down here.
Stop moving.
You heard it too, right?
Footsteps.
Somewhere in here.
Anyway, I wanted to dig here anyway, so let's go.
Yeah, we're gonna go to the right now.
And watch this.
We're making only a single line like this and it's gonna be enough.
Uh, almost.
Hold on.
Like if, like look at this.
You see that?
The width is big enough.
Oh, it's much more efficient.
Oh yeah.
And this way I also dig extremely straight.
But my prediction is I'm gonna end up in the exact same place because I went up for a long time when I was in there last.
Look how nice this tunnel is.
I am ducking though.
Like I barely have space.
Keep going.
I am so afraid of hitting myself with this.
You don't even know.
Maybe you do know.
I fucked it up.
It's not as straight anymore now.
It was good while it lasted.
I wonder if you can stack the plasma beam enhancer and make it even wider.
Imagine that.
Man, I gotta take a piss real bad.
As soon as I hit something here, I'm gonna take a piss.
Actually, no, I'm gonna do it now.
Beer back.
Hold on.
Can I make this more efficient?
How many...
If I just click once.
Two, three.
So, doo doo doo.
Oh yeah, that's faster.
Except I somehow messed it up.
Damn it.
Okay, four is good.
Actually, I'm going a little bit up.
I'm going a little bit down.
There we go.
That's the sweet spot.
Oh man, I'm getting that pooping feeling.
I feel like I'm not supposed to be here.
This feels dirty.
What am I hearing?
Oh, that's from outside my window.
A helicopter.
I don't know what I thought I heard in the game.
Ooh, look at that!
It is the exact same place as I predicted.
Nice!
Make a nice opening here.
Come on, get rid of that.
There we go.
Nice!
Now we're back with a full blood potion and everything.
I'm gonna go up again.
Let's not spend too much water here.
Okay, just a test.
Do I take damage from lava?
Yes, okay.
Okay, so we're not immune from the lava damage, but we are immune from being set on fire.
All this lava is from people I killed.
I'm just tracing the outline here.
Look at how everything is being simulated now because I get close.
So it's similar to Minecraft in that way, where not the entire world is being simulated at all times.
It's only when you're close.
Okay.
Oh my god, the digging is wild!
A skull!
I feel like an archaeologist.
Oh.
I thought I hit something I couldn't dig, but I was wrong.
I can easily dig through this.
I heard something.
I'm hearing a ding.
I'm gonna keep going though.
This place is massive!
Let's take a quick peek.
Dude, it's completely dead.
Whatever this place is,
I'm actually kind of nervous.
Okay, I think the ding is just part of the background.
Why are there no enemies?
What is this place, man?
Dude,
I'm going all the way to the surface almost.
I hear someone.
Oh yeah.
What up, fools?
Got him.
And then we have a nice little repository for the lava so we don't spill everywhere.
Lovely.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
We got lava coming in.
Just let that drip all the way down.
Holy shit!
I was scratching my neck when that guy came down.
Good thing I had reaction times of a master.
Come on, drip, drip, drip, drip, drip.
I don't need to wait.
I can dig.
Stop.
I wonder if this is like their home.
This is where the fire dudes are born.
What the fuck?
A heezy man.
What are you doing here?
Maybe he's also an archaeologist.
Maybe he was sent out with his friends on an expedition into the unknown, just like I am expeditioning the... Ooh, look at this.
Wait, where am I?
Oh, I'm actually out of mana.
Ooh, that's annoying.
Wait.
Oh, wait.
Am I in the hemisphere?
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
I'm afraid of taking that.
The guy will spawn, right?
But I am strong.
Yoink.
I'm leaving.
I'm out of here.
Don't mind me.
Let me actually dig up now.
Look at that.
Ooh, we've got sunlight.
We dug our way up from the bottom of the world all the way to the top.
Mmm.
That's awesome.
You know what?
Let's go to the pyramid.
There's a boss there.
Fuck this desert.
Can I eat the cactus?
No, it's wood.
Never mind.
Okay, so...
Oh!
Oh, wait.
Never mind.
I thought it worked for a second.
Whoops.
What else can I try on that?
What if I destroy it?
Something hiding inside.
You know what?
I'm going to try and destroy this.
Oh, it's really resistant.
Look at that.
Something inside.
Let me get rid of this whole clock.
Okay.
Never mind.
Now we should be encountering a skull in a second here.
Look at me.
Beautiful.
Ah,
hold on.
Oh, wait.
That's right.
I wanted to try and bring a demon eye in here and put it there.
Well, we got to go all the way west to get that one.
So, I don't want to do that now.
But that's for later.
Here we are.
Oh, you know what?
Hold on.
Also, I did go all the way up here, I believe.
This is the same run, right?
Where I know?
Is it actually the same run?
No fucking way.
It is.
And look at that.
Demon eye.
We need the demon eye.
Hold on.
I can't think there.
I want to get through the entrance.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Want teleport?
Want please?
I haven't found a single teleport.
Like, what the hell?
I mean, there's a boss in here that's actually quite easy.
Let's go kick his ass.
But we're going to play it safe still.
Always play it safe.
Is this blue fire even dangerous to me?
It's not.
Okay, perfect.
Wait.
You should be somewhere up here if memory serves correct.
Oh, I see you.
Good.
I had my shield.
Oh, here we are.
Here we are.
It's going to spawn immediately, right?
I need to prepare myself in various ways.
We got to get rid of the slime.
Oh, I don't have a lot of mana.
I mean, water.
Let's just wait for this slime to wear off.
Come on.
There we go.
Slime gone.
Status unslammed.
Oh, you know what?
I have Ambrosia.
I think we're gonna try something here.
Uh, hold on.
How am I gonna do this?
I could just pour it.
Hold
on.
I'm gonna make a little bath up here.
It's gonna seem a little insane, maybe.
Oh, I can't dig through that.
Oh, but I can.
I'm gonna run a nice bath like that.
Rid of that little pixel so I don't get stuck on that.
Look at that.
There we go.
And how long does it stay on me?
Wait, why am I... Oh, there are still particles.
We got to get rid of all these parts.
Somebody got stuck on that during the fight.
That would be disaster.
Am I free?
Okay, so I jump in.
Okay, it lasts quite a while.
But if I jump in and I stand here... Oh, it lasts quite a while.
Let's remember what this boss does.
So he has a shield.
No, wait.
No, no, no.
He opens his mouth or something and I have to shoot him then.
All right, dude.
There we go.
Open your mouth.
Call me Silman Koipi.
Wait.
I'm immune, right?
I'm immune, I'm immune.
Wait, is he also immune then?
Shit.
Get him, get him, get him, get him, get him, get him.
Oh, yeah.
Got you.
Fuck yeah.
What's that?
Recoil damper.
Yo, that's awesome.
And the wand is not bad either.
In fact, I would say it's better than this one because look, minus 18 degrees spread on it too.
And lots of slots.
Thanks.
And we have this.
One in the pond, one in the tree, one on the ledge, one under the sun.
100% referring to the music stuff.
What is that?
Random static projectile spill.
Why is there a black hole icon on it though?
What's that?
Nala.
Um, wait, I hear someone.
Wait, what is that wand?
Fuck, hold on.
I need to get rid of spells.
Get rid, you know what?
Maybe we get rid of the rock.
Yeah, fuck the rock.
We're never gonna find unlimited spells.
I just don't believe it at this point.
That dream is gone.
So I'll blade, I want to keep.
Actually, no, I don't because now I have this digger right here.
I don't need it.
Okay.
Oh, that's my old wand.
So what is this?
Cast one random static projectile spell.
Why is there a black hole symbol on it then if it's random?
What's that?
Copy random spell.
Cast a random spell among the other spells in your wand.
Okay.
And this one was, I think I had this one before.
Oh, wait, no room for it.
Let's remove that one.
The duration of a projectile is set to zero.
Why is that good?
Oh, it does reduce cast a lay quite a bit.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, wait, I can't change now, but.
Why would I want to do that?
What could benefit from having no duration?
Maybe... I don't know.
That's a good question, isn't it?
I wonder what this says.
Joy 117.
No, it's not normal letters for sure.
Need more blood.
Wait, why is this filled with?
No.
Okay.
Well, that was nice.
We gained some HP.
We killed the dude.
Hallelujah.
Let's go down.
I'm exploring this entire pyramid now.
Hopefully, we're going to find some more people that have blood in their veins.
Hamis!
So mean that they're storing you in these jars.
Oh, he's angry.
Look at that.
That's an angry ghost.
You mean, you mad.
You real mad.
Oh, you have a lot of HP.
We have a dude up here with a welding mask on.
So, I don't know what you're shooting, but I don't like it.
Anything these mages shoot scares the crap out of me.
I've had some bad experiences with that.
Slowly healing.
Nice.
Full HP.
Beautiful.
Kind of reminds me of the art this place with the traps on the walls and all that.
By the way, the guy was called Colmi Silma Koipi.
I think it means Colmi Silma copy.
So, and the last boss is called Colmi Silma.
So, maybe it's like a copy of Colmi Silma.
Like a miniature version of it, you know.
God, I hate being slimed.
This game is pretty much simulating what those shows were on Nickelodeon back in the 90s.
You know, all those kids getting slimed in those game shows, it was weird as fuck.
What a weird time that was.
I don't know if that is anything you guys are old enough to remember.
Order this.
Make it safe.
Oh yeah, this is blood right here.
I mean, not that we need it right now.
Look at that.
A hoodlum.
Ah, no more water.
Crap.
I bet finding water down here is going to be a little challenging.
A blue one.
What is the difference?
Remember, guys, I still have that perk that will increase my max HP.
And the more HP I'm gathering right now, that thing is going to be insane.
Ha!
Bounced off my shield.
Oh, that's right.
We have this place.
I remember that sand cave.
Ouch.
Nice water.
Very eerie music in this place.
It's that sort of music that makes me think I shouldn't be here, you know?
We actually got to mark this place on the map.
So it's right below the pyramid.
There's a sand cave.
Let's do that immediately.
I just don't know how big it is, but we're going to do something like this.
Draw a rectangle.
So let's say it starts...
This is to be changed.
It's not accurate yet, because I don't know the dimensions, but...
Sand cave.
It does look like it stops right at the edge of the pyramid, right?
Or at least the brickwork there.
So I think my dimensions are correct on the right side, at least.
Why does this not turn into blood?
It's meat.
Come on, blood me up.
I remember the scary part about this place is that they have these guys here that shoot poison.
And that really fucked me last time.
I got to be careful there.
Dude, what if I just keep digging right?
Let's try it.
And you know what?
I'm going to dig from a point that I remember.
So I'm going to dig from the very top.
Just so I have easy times remembering when I have to draw it.
I'm going everywhere right now, dude.
I don't even care.
Maybe at a slight downward angle, just because I think I'm close to the surface here.
Whoa, good thing I'm fire immune.
I don't know what just happened.
Getting a little toasty in here.
I almost walked into the fucking beam like an idiot.
I'm trying not to move my cursor.
I'm only moving my character just so I keep it straight.
Well, straight line, I mean, not horizontal line.
Oh, it's changing.
Wait a minute, I can...
No way.
Now we're back here.
Bro, this layout is messing with me.
What?
Wait, are we back?
Well, we...
I have not been here, have I?
No, no, no, no, no, no, this is new.
Overgrown cavern.
What the fuck?
Fungal soil.
Hey.
Oh, another broken wand.
I gotta, dude, I gotta go back to the anvil.
I already have one.
Hold on, that is not electric, is it?
Doesn't look like it.
Hold on, overgrown cavern, what the fuck, man?
This is nuts.
So I dig sort of that way.
I'm just gonna assume it's...
Oh, I don't remember the exact distance between the pyramid and the tower.
Let's just draw it where I think it is.
I think it's like...
It didn't go that far.
Maybe like that, dimensions to be changed, of course, depending on what we find.
Overgrown cavern.
Reminds me of, um...
What is that other place called?
Fungal cavern.
Okay.
Glue ball?
Yeah.
Okay.
I kind of want to grab that, though, but I don't want to throw away my ambrosia.
I'm gonna leave it.
And look at the background.
It almost looks like we're still in that same area.
What the hell.
And look at this.
Now we're...
What a weird place.
Good thing I can dig through this.
Whoa!
That's a big fungus.
Okay.
It's acid fungus.
Another wand.
Okay.
Can I please get a teleport?
Teleport, please?
Okay, so that's the edge.
I'm gonna follow the edge again.
Just to see how big this...
Oh, look at this.
That's an ugus kiwi.
I feel like we should leave that alone.
Is this thing gonna explode when I get near it?
Okay, it's not.
That thing stays there.
I'm not messing with it.
No.
Blue sand.
The only other place I've seen this is in...
What's it called?
The place before the last area.
Yo, that's a super low castellae.
Is that even better than this wand?
I think it is.
Although I kind of like this.
But no.
Thanks.
I wish I could change my wands.
It would be glorious.
By the way, every time I've been saying, okay, let's just dig.
I found something every time.
Unless I've been super lucky, I feel like it's always worth it to just dig.
This is very surprising.
Whoa, what a chain reaction.
You saw that?
I killed one of these guys, and the other one's exploded.
Whoa, damn.
Things are popping off in here.
Bro, where are these guys coming from?
Did that thing just grow?
Huh?
Wait, what does it say?
Fungus blood?
Can I drink that?
Dude, there's so many wands here.
Critical unbloody enemies.
No, thanks.
And now we're back in this area.
It's so weird.
That's the Ukuskivi.
Oh, we got a fire, dude.
Bye-bye.
I think I checked this one already.
Yeah.
Yo, hold the HP.
Give me your blood.
Oh, hello.
I'm curious what the spells they shoot is gonna do to me, but I'm not curious enough to let myself get hit.
If I accidentally get hit, I'll...
Guess I'll pay attention.
We've got two of the Uku guys.
Oh, bounced back.
Please don't kill me.
Oh, hello.
They bleed Teleportation.
I've got to be careful around that.
It's way too much lava here.
Oh, wait, I'm confused.
Confusion.
Stop being confused.
Wait, is the aura making me confused?
Oh, my God, it is.
That is such a mean aura.
Holy crap.
That guy has a wand or had a wand.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Dude, these ones are sick.
Oh, this one has two spells per cast.
It's not that great.
I'm not a fan of the more than one spells per cast.
More than one spell per cast makes me pick it up last.
Come here.
This is such a weird place.
Like, look at how it alternates.
Now there's like this part and now we're back in some sort of jungle again.
Or a fungal place.
Oh, nice.
Hell yeah.
Fucking love finding hearts.
It's my favorite.
Manami.
What a place.
More hearts.
This is sick.
Oh, look at this guy.
He had a top hat on.
Another one.
They actually explode quite violently.
Okay.
Holy hand grenades.
No, thanks.
I'm actually kind of scared of those, especially when I don't have...
Oh, he's spreading pollen.
Of course he is.
Fuck you.
How dare you.
Whiskey potion.
Who left a bottle of whiskey in here?
Must be one of the Heezy guys.
There's so many wants here.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, that.
We still got a plate safe here.
Don't get overconfident.
In fact, I have no systematics in my exploration right now.
I am just going where the wind guides me.
And there is no wind down here.
So pretty much nothing is guiding me.
I'm just waddling.
Another wand.
I mean, if this keeps going like this, maybe I will find a teleport at some point.
Polymorphine?
No, thanks.
Water potion?
Yes, please.
Oh, hello there.
And another wand.
Look at the stats on these.
I mean, the mana charge is kind of bad, but...
it's just really good ones.
And what is up here?
Look at this.
Now it sort of goes into this part again.
Okay.
Weird.
Hold on.
If I go straight up from here...
Oh, shit.
I found a deposit of copper.
Hey, guys.
What's up, easy people?
They're just...
hanging out here, it seems.
Fill up my potion.
I am confused.
I'm so confused.
Another copper deposit.
There's got to be a use for the blue sand.
The blue sand seems...
somehow important.
Are you...
are you an enemy?
You like water?
I don't know if I should be doing anything to it.
Look at this fucking place.
I'm gonna go straight up.
Make some resting spots here.
Oh, wait.
Are we back in...
Look at that.
We're back in the desert.
I guess that makes sense.
Oh, we're here.
Wait, I never marked this.
Where exactly is this?
Let me keep going right.
Ah, here we go.
This is that tower.
Watchtower.
In fact, I should just write that on the map.
Move this over a little bit, make it pretty.
There we go.
There.
Watchtower.
And there was something up there.
I kind of want to look at it again.
Let's just...
Dude, I'm exploring the whole world.
This is so much fun, man.
This is what I've been waiting for, man.
Just walking from place to place.
Very powerful.
Just solving the mysteries of this world.
I was up here once before.
And there's a drawing inside of here up here.
But I forgot exactly what it was.
Let's see it again.
Okay, there's lava.
Um...
That's okay.
We're going to drain it.
Oh, wait.
If I just keep doing this, I will evaporate the lava.
Sort of.
I mean, most of it.
Most of it gets evaporated.
Just draining kind of slow, though.
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
And we have another layer.
Oh, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Drain it.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
Okay, let me just draw that, I guess.
Oh!
Oh, I was already...
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Hopefully that wasn't for too long.
I had the overlay on.
Fuck!
I'm sorry, guys.
Damn it!
Okay, I apologize.
I will keep an extra eye on that.
It wasn't for too long, though, because I...
Yeah, it couldn't have been long.
Shit.
God damn it.
Watchtower there.
This is what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna make a little blow-up thing.
This is gonna look so cool.
Watch this.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
I'm gonna start with the box.
I'm gonna go gray.
And a line.
Look at this fucking pro shit.
How cool is that?
Yeah.
That's fine.
Could be better, I guess.
But that's okay.
There we go.
And then I'm gonna draw what I see in the game here.
Which is...
The pond.
Or it could be the lake.
It's hard to say.
And then something in the sky above.
So hold on.
Use a white color here.
Got some fishies here.
Let me zoom in just a bit.
My artistic skills are immaculate.
That's what it shows, right?
Yeah, that's definitely fishes down there.
And then there's something in the sky.
No, actually, it's more like a...
Like that.
And then there's like...
Hanging off of it.
With a question mark on it.
Ooh, very exciting.
So this could either mean the pond or...
The lake, I guess.
So in the game...
It does actually show a mountain on the right.
And something mountain is on the left too.
Right?
So...
I don't know.
Let me also draw it nicely like that.
There we go.
Look at that.
Beautiful stuff.
Look at that blow up.
Isn't that cool?
I like it.
In fact, we're gonna add in one more fish, facing the other way.
Just for completeness sake here.
There we go.
Beautiful fishes.
Bunny fish.
And now I switch back to the game.
I'm so sorry about that before.
I will double check that every time I exit that now.
It needs to be part of my checklist.
Okay.
Now we have a lava problem here.
No we don't!
I reject lava problems.
Now I'm going deeper.
That's right.
I remember this.
I briefly explored this stuff last time.
Oh, you know, I can just go around.
Yo!
Oh wait, I'm O2-ing!
Shit.
Wait, I can dig through this?
No way!
Wait a minute.
Let's be careful here.
We're gonna drain all the...
Okay, watch this.
I'm gonna make a channel.
Oh, I'm out of mana.
No way.
Maybe I shouldn't have dug all the way down.
I regret.
I regret my decision.
This is fine.
All of it!
Uh-oh.
Don't drain it this way.
Yeah, we're just gonna wait for that.
And while that's draining, I'm just gonna have a look around.
What's going on here?
Look at all this sand.
It's crazy that I can dig through the brickwork like that.
Ooh, be careful.
It's gonna take a while.
Listen to that sound.
That's actually a very pleasing sound.
All right, well, now we explored that.
So we know that this stuff is right underneath the watchtower.
Or like, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
That's actually big.
That's big.
We're gonna draw that.
Overgrown cavern.
We need to extend this.
And make it bigger.
It's actually really big.
Something like that.
Now I've been here.
In fact, I'm actually gonna write this on my to-do list as well.
What I just discovered.
Otherwise, I will forget.
Okay.
I want to write...
What should I write?
I should write...
Explore the
heavens.
Above pond slash lake.
There we go.
What else do I have on this?
Demon eye and fungal caverns.
Try teleportation with eye and snow adepts.
Figure out the music box riddle.
Yeah.
And murder boss in ancient laboratory.
Yep, I've got stuff to do.
But I'm definitely not going to try that boss without having first...
gotten the HP buff perk that I have somewhere down there in the depths.
We're gonna need to get that first.
Oh, let's be careful here.
This is a dangerous place, man.
Whoop.
Oh, nice.
HP in the house.
16k gold as well.
I'm rich.
Another HP.
What is happening?
And a crazy wand.
Look at the mana charge on this one.
Holy shit.
Dude, I may have to take it.
It's too good.
Holy damn.
This place is overflowing with wands.
What a wonderful feeling this is.
Exploring.
Huh?
Wait, what?
Uh...
Say what now?
That was weird.
Those were the prickly spore pods.
Oh, god.
I hear... that sound makes me uneasy.
Those little stupid frog-looking creatures make me uneasy.
No, very few things make me easy.
It's always uneasy.
I think these things just pop out of nowhere.
Where are you coming from?
Huh?
What's that?
The circular...
Ooh.
Oh, dope.
These things grow weirdly and then explode and then come back and it's very weird.
Another wand.
Oh, I took a lot of damage from that.
We gotta be safe distance from these guys.
I need blood.
Permation trifurcated.
Cast three spells in a trifurcated pattern.
Hm.
Nah.
Shit.
There was also a place with an Ukuskivi.
I forgot where it was.
Is that lava?
Holy shit.
No.
No, thanks.
There's way too much lava here for my taste.
Yeah.
Oh, this place is massive.
That is a sick wand as well.
This is the place for wands, man.
Holy shit.
Did you see that explosion?
It's like when they explode, they also trigger all the nearby weird fungus somehow.
And make that explode too.
That's what it feels like.
Oh no, look at how many there are of these.
I'm just gonna hold my ground here and wait for them to come.
Mystery fungus.
Say what?
We gotta eat that immediately.
Hold on.
Let me take care of these first.
Feel in harmony with the magical forces.
Cause ingesting mystery fungus and more.
Say what?
Holy shit.
Okay.
Listen to the sound.
Oh, I don't want to be tripping down here, man.
This is already a trip in itself.
I need blood.
Actually, there was blood.
Grab it.
Drink from the floor.
What's this?
Missiles.
So many wands.
Overgrown caverns.
There's actually gold in these walls too.
Camus is my friend.
Kill them all.
Now we go up.
Look, a hoodlum.
Give me your blood.
Is that one of mine?
Oh, I checked that one already.
Dude, this place is massive.
Is that flamoxium?
It is.
Look at this.
These hammers are drunk.
They're celebrating Sunday over there.
Look at that.
I'm gonna go pet them.
They're too cute.
There.
They have been adequately petted now.
Always pet the h...
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, I'm...
Oh, I see.
I was drunk.
I thought I somehow gained like a triplicate shot effect on my spell or something.
Part of me wants to just go over there and crack open a cold one with the hemises.
A deadly heal.
And that wand is sick.
A small castellate, decent recharge.
Hold on, there's a guy over here.
Where are you?
Oh, he has a wand.
Emergency stations.
Okay, he's down.
Target eliminated.
What's on this thing?
Critical on burning.
Chaos Larpa.
Giant spitter bolt.
Huh.
I really wish I could edit my wands everywhere, because I would be experimenting so much right now.
I just don't have anywhere nearby that I can change my wands, man.
It sucks.
Now this one.
I'm taking that.
So let me see here.
Right.
Um...
So, do I have anything?
Maybe with the Nala.
The duration of a projectile is set to zero, so maybe that means it explodes right when I shoot it, so that I get hit by it or something.
Or I get the effect.
You know, maybe that's the use for that.
Or, I did also find a spell somewhere.
That, like the orbit spell, remember?
I just forget where I found that.
I just really forget.
Holy shit, guys.
Calm down.
Look how many fucking frog creatures there are.
Shit.
I think I've seen this one before.
Shit, shit, shit.
Wand.
Look at how that looks!
Whoa!
Look at all that crap!
Rec... increases the recoil.
Interesting.
Water to poison.
Damage field.
Okay, actually, there's not really that much here that I am intrigued by.
This looked way crazier at first glance.
It's just not that great, I guess.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
It's kind of great, but...
I am picky at this point in time.
Wait, how are these guys being spawned all the time?
Uh-oh.
Why are these things growing?
There's a weird chain effect going on over there.
Shit, that damaged me a lot.
Anything in this?
Oh, we've got toxic rock here.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm actually too scared.
We gotta take care of that, dude.
Explode all that.
Can I thank you, toxic rock?
Yo, I can totally just remove it.
I disregard toxic rock.
I reject.
I say no to that.
Fuck the toxic rock, man.
If you don't like something, just get rid of it.
Easy peasy.
Piercing shot.
Makes a projectile fly through enemies but harmful to the caster.
No.
I still don't understand quite the use for that one.
There's a wand up there, too.
Look at that, explosion confetti.
This guy has ambrosia on him.
We don't like that.
What?
I'm taking way too much damage here.
There's some kind of chain reaction happening up here, and I don't understand what's going on.
Are we done?
Huh?
I have no clue.
These things keep regrowing as well.
There's something down here doing something.
It's you.
Stop it.
All right.
You know what?
I'm just gonna dig around it.
This place is nuts.
Oh, be careful.
Those guys explode.
What's that?
Blue glimmer and ice balls.
The blue glimmer does reduce castellae.
It's actually a good spell to have.
What's this?
Gold plus fungal soil pouch?
Really?
Hold on.
How much gold?
Mostly gold.
Wow.
Sure.
Let's make a pile of gold.
We do actually need the money, believe it or not.
Because we have one perk left, okay?
And if I'm not happy with that perk, we have to re-roll a bunch of times.
So we need all the money we can get.
I don't want to make the last perk a shit perk.
It needs to be great.
Okay, now get rid of this.
Boing.
Grab that again.
Let's check out this wand over here.
Whoa!
Damn.
All right.
No.
I feel like I'm going into places I shouldn't go here.
This is... I gotta start heading back to heal.
Oh, hold on.
I see you up there.
Do not.
You asshole.
Come on now.
Look at all that pollen.
My worst nightmare.
Gotcha.
Oh, there's something in here.
Stop doing that thing, whatever it is.
Holy shit.
Wait, whatever was in here is gone now.
I think it was a flask of something.
This is a... wild place.
Okay, we got some blood here.
That's something.
Drink, drink, drink.
We're getting a little high in the process, but that's okay.
I'm not risking any highness.
Your highness.
This run is too good.
All right, it's time we hit up and grab some blood and heal up.
We're making our way back.
What is that?
The fungus is vibrating.
Oh, now it's gone.
Ukuskivi.
I guess I'll go back to where I dug before.
No, wait.
Yes.
Yes, I am.
No, wait.
I'm just going straight up.
Gotta play this safe.
Okay, so here's the plan.
I'm actually just going to go through all the biomes from top to bottom now.
Find blood, heal up, grab all the hearts that I missed.
And then when we get all the way down, I'm going to grab the extra heart perk.
And then we go one level deeper and we grab the remaining perk we have.
Why can't I...
Something's blocking the path.
And this time I'm not going to dig into an Ukuskivi filled water chamber.
Nope, that will not happen.
Mark my words.
Maybe just explore a bit on the way.
There's some blood here.
Not bad.
Let's wait.
This is the sand cave.
Okay, change of plans.
We're going to just explore the sand cave a little bit more.
Because there are humanoid enemies here we can kill and get blood from.
Especially look at all that blood over there.
Oh yeah, that is what I'm talking about baby!
Exactly what I need.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Although I feel like I should have gotten more blood out of that.
That was a very disappointing amount of blood.
Shit, I broke a hole in it.
Maybe they did.
These assholes.
Someone's shooting.
Oh, it's the poison dude.
Hate the poison dude.
Yeah, we're doing sand cave.
I love the music here.
Perfectly encapsulates how I feel when I explore areas like this.
Eerie atmosphere.
I'm starting to reach the point where I have so much HP that healing with blood is going to take a while.
Okay, we're getting up there though.
Boom!
Bada boom!
Big bada boom!
How dare you!
Yes!
Oh, uh-oh.
Not scary.
What's up fools?
Oh no, it's the poison!
Shit.
Don't you poison me.
Holy shit, there's gonna be so much blood here.
I can't wait.
I feel like I'm destroying the blood.
Is the digging blast actually destroying blood?
I need a chainsaw, man.
To really cut up these fools.
Because this is destroying it.
It's not actually cutting it up.
Wow.
That really scared me.
Grab all the blood.
Look at my HP.
I have a lot.
No friendos.
Where my friendos at?
Not that I have any pheromone anyway, but still.
Man, the sand- Ooh, what do we have here?
Oh, okay, hold on.
In case a boss spawns, I'm gonna get the fuck out.
I need to prepare myself mentally here.
Also, I gotta grab some of this blood.
What the fuck is that skull?
Uh-oh.
Heal.
More.
Massive healing.
Full health.
Oh, hold on.
What's up, dude?
Secrets of undeath have been unlocked to you.
Hold on.
Get rid of...
Uh, that one.
Makes corpses of creatures killed by a projectile.
Rise to your aid.
Ooh, interesting.
Please no boss.
Okay, we have five orbs now.
I don't know if I've ever had that many.
Also, I kinda wanna...
I don't like this.
I never use these.
But why am I getting this?
No, I don't like this.
I'm taking this back.
I do have a better homing, so.
Fill up my flask.
Okay, no boss, I guess.
Cool.
So there's one of these places in the sand cave.
That's good to know, man.
And that's the bottom?
Look at that.
So the sand cave has a bottom.
Kinda wanna dig through it.
See where I get to.
I am not stopped by simple dense rock anymore.
I'm not limited by those things.
No, sir.
Okay, we fall on that.
Ouch!
Asshole.
Are we safe?
Good.
I'm gonna mark it.
So we...
We went quite far down.
So hold on.
Oh, sand cave's over here.
So I was in there before.
Wait a minute.
I think I'm...
I think I have this wrong.
Didn't I go straight down from the watchtower?
Like there was all the lava.
Or was it over here?
In any case, I'm just gonna draw it in here.
We can always change it later, I guess.
We're gonna make a...
I don't even know what to draw.
In fact, I need to...
I basically need to make a template for this sort of room.
Because I've seen this like a million times in this game.
It's also on the other side of the lava lake.
So I need to make a...
A lot...
Make it a bit smaller, like that.
And there's like...
The layout is sort of like a...
What should I call it?
Something like that.
And there's this...
Place like that.
And it has these pillars.
You
know, something like that.
I'm gonna purify this later.
Just to get a rough outline of this.
And then inside, there's always...
Actually, sometimes there's hearts.
And other times, there's like a spell.
Let me make that in yellow.
I'm just gonna make a...
Heart.
And there's actually also a...
Oh wait, did I even read this tablet?
Hold on.
Oh, I never think I did.
Hold on a second.
I don't think I actually looked at it.
Back.
Also not.
Okay, so it's like shaped like that.
Oh, there's a little platform in the center, that's right.
Have I seen this one before?
Emerald Tablet, Volume 4.
Oh, this is new.
The definition of death is the disjunction of the composite.
But there is no disjunction of that which is simple.
For it is one.
Death consists in the separation of the soul from the body.
Because anything formed out of two, three, or four components must disintegrate.
And this is death.
Understand further that no complex substance which lacks fire eats.
Drinks or sleeps.
Because in all things which have a spirit, fire is that which eats.
What the fuck are you on about?
The definition of death.
Hold on, what does disjunction mean?
I'm just gonna quickly Google that.
Disjunction.
Oh god, I have 7% battery on my phone.
A lack of correspondence or consistency.
Oh, it's like something is disjointed?
There is a disjunction between the skills taught in education and those demanded in the labor market.
Okay, yeah, so like... yeah.
Got it.
The definition of death is the disjunction of the composite.
But there is no disjunction of that which is simple.
So we have composite and we have simple.
For it is one.
Death consists in the separation of the soul from the body.
Because anything formed out of two, three, or four components must disintegrate.
And this is death.
Understand further that no complex substance which lacks fire eats drinks or sleeps.
Because in all things which have a spirit, fire is that which eats.
Is it like saying every creatures have a fire inside of them?
And all creatures are complex composites?
And dying is like separating those complex composites from one another?
Like separating the soul from the body?
Okay.
I'm actually going to take a picture of this with my phone just because I think I need to note down all these.
I need to make like a catalog of all these tablets writings at some point.
Okay, let's move on.
Oh, fuck that scared the crap out of me.
Holy shit.
I jumped in my chair.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
I need to calm down.
Holy shit.
I was not ready for that.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Some blood here.
Okay, that's the danger of digging so fast.
And digging on autopilot like I was, you know.
Gotta look where you dig.
Kind of important.
Let's grab some water.
Ow!
I was bathing, you asshole.
Just having a nice bath.
Then you come along.
Got the water only, thank you.
I almost did it again.
Caught myself in time though.
Fool me once, shame on you.
Fool me twice, shame on you.
Fool me three times, also shame on you.
But like seven times, shame on me.
Dude, I am slowly becoming a god in this game.
What I mean is my character is so powerful.
Nothing can stop me.
It's lovely.
Feels good to be a god, man.
I got a poison man.
I see you there.
Don't even think about it.
Man, this is the place to get blood.
There's just so many humanoids.
Where are you?
Stop!
So, if I just keep going down here...
At some point, I'm going to reach the bottom, right?
I was there before.
Unless that bottom is at this different elevation over here than it was on the right.
Can you stop shooting those balls at me?
Look at all that blood.
Man, the fire resistance is just incredible.
And here's the bottom.
Okay.
Let's see if there's anything on the left here.
Bottom.
Okay, so what I'm going to do now...
I'm going to dig left.
We got to get an idea of where exactly this edge is in the world.
And let's see where we end up.
It's going to take a while.
One, two, three, four.
That's all.
Wait, look at this.
Wait!
Oh, never mind.
It's not going to take a while.
Wait a minute.
Do I have it all wrong?
So I guess there's also some
kind of area there to be named in the future.
Let's keep going along the outline here.
Oh, wait.
Have I been here?
It seems like there's light over here as if I've explored it.
And this definitely goes further down than on this side on the right.
Let's be careful here.
Don't dig too fast.
Just in case.
Goes really far down.
This has to be the same area I was in.
Just from the other side now.
Oh, what the fuck is that?
Something's hanging.
What are you?
Little fireman.
Meat realm.
What?
The fuck is this?
Meat?
No!
It's all meat!
Guys, this game is nuts!
You know what I love?
The developers are like, okay, so here's Noiter.
It's a roguelike.
You're a wizard.
You get to shoot once, right?
And here are the levels.
Go.
Kill the final boss, you win.
But actually, what they don't tell you...
is that the game is way bigger.
I keep finding new shit.
There's no indication at all in the game.
That this is here.
Okay.
We've got a very aggressive sniper man.
But I have infinite healing, so hey.
All's good, bro.
Wait a minute.
Something's wrong.
Something's wrong!
This is not healing me!
This is some cursed blood!
Who is the sniper?
No, it's all... is this also cursed?
Okay, so I want to kill that guy over there.
Where are you, fucker?
Also, we gotta be careful.
Don't drown.
Don't drown in blood.
Hey, fuckface!
There you are.
Dude, it's like a pumped up version of a Heezy sniper.
Can I drink the blood from the enemies, though?
I know I can't do the floor.
No, I can't.
I can't.
This is terrible.
Also, I'm losing HP quick.
You know what?
This place seems a little hardcore.
I say we come back here when we have gained some more HP.
Meaning, we get the perk that gives us extra HP.
This is just... I'm too scared.
Let's mark it.
That we can do.
So, whatever this place is called, I don't know.
Whatever, right?
Something.
But then, there's sort of a loosely connected area.
It's actually the same area, I guess.
A little further down, like here.
And it was called Meat Realm.
What a name.
That's appropriate, I think.
Yep.
I am going to go left now.
Left, left, left, left, left.
Look, I've been... yeah.
You see that?
That's the other side.
It's the same area I was in.
Wow.
Hold on a fucking second.
That means...
Oh, wait a second, then.
The proportions here are all off here.
Because this needs to somehow connect there.
So, I guess I have this all wrong here.
That the proportions there are completely fucked.
So, I'm going to say that this is probably incorrect there.
I'm going to move this stuff there.
I can still put that there, I guess.
Get rid of this.
Whoops.
To be predified later.
Oh no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, maybe.
And then when I dug before here...
That's why it took so long to dig.
Because I went all the way to that wall.
Right?
And then, how does that connect there?
I guess it's...
No, wait a second, this doesn't make any sense what I just did.
Oh, I connected it wrong, I connected it wrong.
I see now, I see now.
This needs to go all the way to here.
No, wait, something's wrong here.
Ah, you know what?
We're going to... whoops.
This whole area right here...
is... to be determined.
We're going to get back there and scout it out, okay?
There's no point in theorizing how it looks.
We got to explore it.
Yeah, okay.
So basically, what I could do now is to go down and left.
But I'm actually just going to go left from here.
I am making... I'm punching holes through the entire world.
And it feels good.
So I think I'm going to be appearing in...
let's say, Easy Base.
I think I'm quite far up compared to the one tunnel I made down below.
My character looks so focused when he's like bent down in the tunnel.
Like he's taking a real...
close look.
Wait a minute.
The fuck is that?
Oh, oh wait, I can still dig it though.
Huh?
Extremely dense.
Hold on, we got to get the outline.
Ah, I'm buried.
There's markings on it.
Oh, I'm out of mana.
Shit.
Ah, we got to wait a bit.
I'll just use this for now.
Dude, it's like...
it's only like a little part.
Look at this.
It's not a whole area.
It's like something.
I found something.
Get rid of all the sand.
I found something in here, man.
That's what I'm saying.
Every time I dig, I find something.
Okay, we recharge now.
I feel like an archaeologist.
The fuck is this?
This is amazing.
Obviously, we got to put something in there.
Yo, there's also something in the back there.
Look at that.
Get rid of all the sand.
I'm scared of accidentally destroying this.
Because remember the hourglass.
When I destroyed the glass, everything collapsed and I actually died.
I'm afraid of hurting this.
It does say extremely dense rock though.
Wait, check, check, check.
Okay, we're fine.
We're fine.
Look at the background.
Doesn't that kind of look like a tablet?
You see that?
Maybe we put a tablet inside of here somehow.
What else am I seeing?
Sort
of...
Let's think about this.
This right here is a tablet for sure.
I mean, I know there's a tablet.
Oh, but I would...
Oh, wait, how do I even get that in there?
I would need some kind of long-distance cast.
No, I can't even do that.
Hold on.
I mean, obviously, I need to put something in here.
The question is, how do I get it in?
I could make a hole with my laser beam, but I'm afraid that I will destroy whatever is going on here.
This is like my one chance to do something here similar to the hourglass, right?
I don't want to mess it up.
I have one shot at this.
Okay, let's look around for some clues.
Where's this located in the world?
Hold on.
Wait a minute, is that...
Wait a second.
So, I definitely docked to the left.
Wait!
Obviously, the proportions here are fucked because...
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, there's definitely more room here, right?
Because we know there's a whole room here, where there's a boss, and there's just no way.
So, we need to move all of this, basically, to the right, to make room.
So, that's to be done later.
But I docked somewhere here, that way.
So, that means, whatever this room is, it's somewhere in between...
So, there's this room with the boss, right?
Somewhere in between there.
Very cool.
Oh, let me also just do that.
Interesting.
And it's to the left.
It's underneath the huge skull, sort of.
Or not really, but kinda.
It's like that area, right?
Okay, maybe that's not a clue.
Mmm.
Ambrosia.
What if I pour that on it?
Yeah, it's not gonna go through.
What if I drink?
It just gets satiated.
I think I need a tablet here.
Like, look at the background.
That's my only clue, right now.
Let me put this on.
That can stay here, I guess.
I'm gonna go grab the...
Oh, wait, no, no, no.
There's a tablet actually somewhere over here.
Okay, let's leave this area for now.
I'll be back.
Let's keep digging left.
I need to find, figure out a method to put liquids inside of something without making a hole.
Is that even possible?
That's like the question, right?
I can pour liquid.
Hey, actually, there are spells that convert liquids, right?
Very mysterious.
Let's also see how long I have to dig before I arrive at the place that I suspect I will arrive at.
Every time I dig, I find something.
I wouldn't be surprised if I find something else when I keep digging here.
Wait, there's quite a distance here.
So my proportions are way off on the map, obviously.
Oh, I hear something.
Let's be careful.
No fucking way!
What are the chances I hit this spot?
I've been here.
No, I've not been here.
Uh...
Stuart, is that you?
My dude, how you doing?
How you doing?
I want to go up here now.
Dude, there's so many mysteries!
Okay, so the next thing I want to try with this is to put teleportation inside, just because of the eye, right, and all that.
But I don't have any.
So that's on my to-do list as well.
Do I want any of these?
I don't think I do.
I don't want water.
I want this...
Actually, I want this spell, just with blood.
Can I please have that?
That would be amazing.
You know what, actually?
I'm gonna go back to the right now and grab the broken wand.
Come on.
Because I'm gonna put it on the anvil.
Who knows, maybe I get a nice spell.
I need teleport.
That's something I really need.
Doop-doop-doop.
God, I need to take a piss again.
Hold on, I need to grab this first.
Wait a second!
There's flowers growing here now!
Hold on, that's gotta be a hint.
Maybe we...
Water the flowers.
What?
The flower disappeared.
Huh?
It's an optical illusion.
Did you see that the flower just disappeared?
What is going on?
There's some kind of mirage stuff happening here.
That is so weird.
Anyway, I got the broken wand.
Let's keep going.
This game is such a mystery.
Where does the water come from?
Oh right, because I made a hole over here in the water.
Basin.
It makes sense.
My man!
I like that the music plays whenever I'm near him.
Okay, we gotta get some blood here.
Wait, what?
Thank God.
I thought for some reason all blood hurt me now.
You know, like I was cursed or something?
Thank God that's not the case.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, my friend.
Consume that blood.
Have I even been here or is this because this place is dark?
No, I have been here.
Yeah, look at that.
Hey, a black hole.
Cool.
White hole.
I don't think I ever tried this.
An orb of positive energy that destroys everything in its path.
Very interesting.
So it destroys everything in its path.
And what did the other one say?
That eats through all obstacles.
So destroys everything.
I don't think it's the same thing.
But you know what?
Hold on.
I'm gonna leave this here because I know where it is.
It's next to the anvil.
I'm gonna go up to the Holy Temple now.
Whoops.
Thought that was a turret.
And it's finally time to change once.
And update our situation.
And I also want to experiment with the healing I just found.
Oh, hold on.
We gotta grab this blood.
We gotta do that.
Ouch.
Hey, dude.
Polymorphine.
I actually don't want to heal all the way up.
So I can experiment with the healing spells.
Here we are.
Oh, wait.
I didn't...
I need to make a hole.
I can do that here.
Feels so naughty going back here.
Whoops.
Diggity-dick.
This is sick.
Make it nice.
There we go.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
We still have all these spells.
Never bought.
Do I want them?
I don't think I do.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yes, I do!
Oh, spiral lock.
Hold up a second.
Also, I gotta experiment with these spells that I found.
Oh, my God.
We have so much ahead of us.
It's gonna be glorious.
You're not allowed in my abode, in my home.
Why is this all dark here?
What is all this?
Oh, chain bolt.
Oh, man.
The chain bolt carried me.
Feels like an eternity ago when I was here, remember?
I was here fighting Stuart.
It was a mess.
I almost died here and stuff.
These are good memories.
Well, sort of.
Okay, I gotta take a piss real quick.
I'll be right back.
Hey, welcome back.
I made myself a small sandwich as well.
So I'm gonna be slightly eating that.
Okay.
I think I can do things with that.
I just need to spiral it up.
So watch this.
If I do that...
Ooh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's a little...
Wait.
Did that heal me?
Five, eight, seven.
Shit, I'm wasting all my ammo.
Well, I guess I have spell refreshers here and there.
That did not heal me.
That went through me.
Shit.
Mmm.
A projectile that at first deals damage, then heals over time.
So hold on.
If I remove that...
Let me just try something.
I'm gonna shoot it up and then quickly catch it.
We need more water.
Okay, let's try now.
Wait, I gotta be faster?
Shit.
Not fast enough.
I need a bit more water in there.
By the way, what if I made like a pool of slime instead?
That's like more viscous.
Maybe that will slow the projectiles down even more.
I can't believe I didn't think about that.
Okay.
Oh, five, eight, seven.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
No, it's not working.
Hmm.
I guess...
Ah, dude.
I think I know what's happening.
It deals damage at first, then heals over time.
But it's not...
There's no friendly fire on it.
So basically, I need bloodlust or something similar.
That will make it lethal.
I want to try this one now.
Random static projectile, but we've got to put that on a trigger for sure.
And you know what?
Let's go somewhere safe.
I don't want to do that up here.
Oh, I'm so scared.
Let's find a nice open area.
Maybe like here.
I shoot it down there.
Let's see what it does.
So it has a black hole image on it.
For a second, I thought it transported this contraption over there because that appeared and that disappeared at the same time.
That totally mindfucked me.
Oh, that's a gig of black hole, isn't it?
That's cool, though.
I like it.
Boing.
What happened down there?
Whoa!
The fuck is that?
That's...
Oh.
Oh, yeah, it's like a suction field.
Of sorts.
Okay, so it actually just does exactly what it says.
It casts a random-ass static projectile.
Why is that good?
Like, why would you ever want randomness like that?
I don't understand.
Unless you can somehow force it to cast something else.
Like something specific, you know?
Because the randomness is bad.
At least I don't see a good use for that.
Okay.
What about copy random spell thrice?
Cast a random spell.
So I can definitely remove the randomness there by having just one spell in my wand, right?
So let's say I do...
I don't know.
Maybe...
Let's try a black hole.
Because I need to test something else on top of this.
Oh, wait, is it a...
Oh, it's an other type.
It's not a projectile modifier.
Is it in the same direction as well?
Let's see.
Wait, that did nothing.
It's gotta be...
It's gotta come first then.
I think...
Was that three?
Because it looked much brighter than usual.
As if they were stacked on top of each other, you know what I mean?
Wait a minute.
That's kind of amazing.
Because that means I get three for the cost of one.
Let me confirm.
Oh, no, no, no.
Put this here.
Put that there.
Oh, hold on.
Before we do this, let's see.
Let's just have a look.
Looks like that.
Okay.
That's insane!
That's a...
That's a big deal.
Look!
Why did it go boom?
Though that's what I don't understand just there.
Maybe because it went empty.
Maybe when you empty a spell, that's like the sound that it makes.
Okay, so duration of a spell is set to zero.
Let's try that now.
What if we just do this?
Okay.
Give me some things like that.
Huh.
Wow.
Okay, so it's not...
It's not like zero, zero.
It's like very close to zero, I guess.
Sorry, I'm randomly eating.
Why would I want that though?
That's the question here.
Why would I want to shorten a spell like that?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, but wait, I can't...
I can't catch it in time then, of course.
I'm too slow.
Interesting.
Oh, copy random spell.
Cast a random spell among the spells in your wand.
So that is the same as that.
Instead of three times, it's just one.
Oh, wait a minute.
I understand why this is super useful now.
Dude!
Oh, but it costs 50 mana.
We're gonna go oom.
Wait.
Oh, wait, it also...
Why is that so slow now?
Oh, no, wait, it's like it's determining between that one and that one, I think.
I can't specify this one.
Ah, crap.
I kind of want to try Necromancy.
Make corpses of creatures killed by a projectile rise to your aid.
And that costs 20 mana.
We can do that and just try it real quick.
I saw a guy down here somewhere.
Otherwise, we'll find one.
Levitation and whiskey.
Oh, there we go.
Why is this good?
Rise to my aid?
What do you mean?
Are they fighting for me?
Oh, there's an enemy over here.
Come here.
Fight for me.
Go!
It works on mechanical enemies, too.
Wait, I wonder if this thing's gonna shoot now.
Are you gonna shoot enemies for me?
There's absolutely no way.
Fight for me.
It's not doing anything.
Is it?
I guess it is distracting them a little bit.
Look, it's shooting towards my followers now.
I mean, that's kind of dope, I guess.
But it's not, like, insane by any means.
It's just kind of neat, I guess.
What's that?
Oh.
Okay, cool.
Now we know what that does.
Very nice.
Back up.
Remove it.
Okay.
What else should I try?
Weakening curse explosives.
I don't have any explosive damage.
But it could be cool to have.
I don't think I like this very much.
All I need is explosive immunity as well.
Then I can go nuts.
Dude, imagine...
You remember the static projectile just called explosion?
Imagine just having that with no trigger.
Just running around, exploding yourself everywhere.
Just killing everything.
If you have explosion immunity.
With this one on as well.
So everyone takes extra damage from it.
That sounds a little bit wild.
But I love it.
Okay.
Oh, dude!
I just had an idea.
I know a way to make this deadly.
We get the fucking piercing.
Because that makes the projectiles damage me.
Oh, but wait, they also fly through me.
So is it gonna fly through me and damage me?
Or just fly through me?
Oh, that's actually interesting.
We got a...
Where the fuck did I get that?
I got that somewhere in this run.
I don't remember.
But if I find it again, I'm gonna try it.
Put this down here.
Nah, actually put it on this wand.
This is like my...
I'm gonna transport...
This is my transport wand.
Maybe I should find a wand that is like...
Oh, hold on.
852.55.
How is this not just a better version of that wand?
Like right now.
Hello?
Look!
I never run out!
It's just better!
Even better, we're gonna go triple into that.
Oh, yeah, it doesn't get better than this.
Unless...
Oh.
Oh, damn.
Is that actually digging just as well?
So the digging power now is actually limited by the firing rate of the spark bolt with double trigger.
That is awesome.
What am I limited by?
Recharge time, 0.35.
These remove 0.5 in total.
These also remove recharge...
Wait, what am I limited by?
Why am I not shooting faster?
Eh?
Why isn't this a continuous brrr?
Maybe that is what counts as continuous brrr.
Let me try only one.
That faster?
I kind of like being able to dig at a distance.
You know?
It's kind of nice.
Hold on, did I have other spells here that...
had a trigger on them?
Didn't I have a magic arrow with a trigger or something?
Hmm.
Oh, wait a minute.
I just had an idea.
Instead of that, let's try this.
I can spread it out a little bit.
This is gonna produce some crazy digging, is it not?
Wait, is that doing anything at all?
Hold up a second.
Oh, it's not really...
I guess it's not spreading out much because it's spreading out at the impact site anyway.
So the digging is not actually doing shit.
I didn't think about that, of course.
But what I can do is, instead of putting that on a trigger...
If I now do...
Hold on, I gotta go back up here.
Like that.
Nah, it's...
It actually costs mana as well.
Just go back to this.
Yeah, I think this is fine.
Hold on, what did I have here before?
Didn't I have something there?
I don't remember.
Hold on, oh wait, what if I put this here?
Okay, so it's instantly...
But it's still digging in that little time frame.
It's not, okay.
I thought maybe I could get the same amount of digging, but without having the danger of having the beam being active like that.
But I guess that's not how that works.
Like it sets the duration to zero, but it doesn't compress all the damage it would do in the original time frame.
Down to zero, you know what I mean?
Okay.
Man, I feel like I had something else on this, and I don't remember what it was.
But I guess maybe I didn't.
This is a fantastic digging wand now.
All I could ask for.
Now I just need to find a big wand that I can use as a transport.
And I think I had one somewhere.
Oh, this one actually has a trigger on it too.
I don't want that though.
Uh, sort this.
What do I not want here?
I think I'm actually good.
Question, do I even need black holes anymore?
Because I'm using a laser cutter.
You know what?
I'm going to keep one black hole, just in case, but I'm not actually going to transport them around because I have this.
And this one right here also seems kind of...
I don't want to say useless.
There's obviously going to be a use for it somehow.
I just haven't discovered it yet.
Uh, pick up some stuff that I want to take with me.
Maybe that's nice to have.
This one I'm actually a little intrigued by.
Yeah, give me that.
All right, this looks good.
All right, cool.
Let's move on.
Let's just double check.
That's working great.
We have this thing right here.
Let's go.
So what is the plan now?
Plan is to eat a little bit of food here.
I want to get to explore this whole region.
I got to find the hearts that I missed.
Hey, guys.
Oh, it's a friendo.
Unfortunately, I don't have pheromone for you, buddy.
Maybe I'll find some.
I'm going to leave you alive.
I do wonder if the healing they do is like based on how much health I have or if it's like static.
You know what I mean?
Because that would mean they could heal me fast if I have a lot of HP.
Or like the same at the same speed, basically, as when I have low and high HP.
Is it percentage based?
That's what I'm wondering.
Okay, stand here.
Oh, I'm slippery.
Hold on.
Can I just burn off the oil?
No?
Come on, man.
I feel like that should work.
Dick.
What's that?
Oh, okay.
Whoops!
I'm just going to die to that vapor.
Let me drink your blood.
Good.
And now I'm slowly going to make my way down to my perk.
It's perk time, baby.
And then maybe, you know what?
After that, maybe it's time to go back to the ancient laboratory and get some revenge.
It's personal at this point.
Hey, you want some?
This is the Arboretum.
Oh, that's scary.
I got to blow that up.
It is kind of risky to dig through snow like that because sometimes there's a propane tank embedded in the snow.
But I'm still going to do it.
I need water.
Can I not fit through there?
Oh, man.
Fine.
Make blood for me.
Oh, look at all that meat.
Yes.
Good.
We're back on top.
Oh, look at all this blood.
Fantastic.
I even have a slot free up here.
So if I find anything, I can take it.
Imagine getting a perk where you get like five extra slots for things.
Wouldn't that be nice?
I mean, I still haven't discovered most.
How the fuck have I not?
How am I at half discovery of perks?
I'm at 50 percent?
What?
I feel like I see the same perks again and again.
There's no way.
How is this possible?
The hell?
I feel like I always see the same perks.
Oh, I have full blood.
Holy shit.
Would you look at that?
This is the spot to go if you want to refill your water and blood.
Load up.
What is even going on here?
More blood.
Jesus.
Oh, yes!
Thank you, Mr. President.
Oh my god, the blood here is wild.
Pheromone!
Uh, we need a flask.
I know there's flasks here somewhere because there's a bar.
They had a siesta there.
Release the blood.
Where's this bar?
Just find the lights, I guess.
Yeah, it's going to be a hell to find, isn't it?
What do we got here?
It's actually safer to dig like this in the snow.
Just because of those propane tanks.
Ah, no, this is the arboretum.
Sturdy construction.
I have no clue where that bar was.
Wait, you're not dying to the...
What?
He took no damage from the drill.
That's weird.
Okay.
More hearts, please.
This place is a nightmare, though, because you can't tell where you've been.
It's all dark.
All the time.
Why is there so much blood?
Oh, here we go.
That's an Ukuskivi.
I think I remember this spot as well.
Can I destroy the Ukuskivi, man?
I could take it.
There we go.
Okay, I've been here.
The unstable polymorphine.
This is the top layer.
I think I might just give up on finding that bar.
It's over.
That thing is lost to the ether.
Go through.
Now, what did I have in this spot?
What was that one again?
The personal gravity field, right?
Look at all this crap I have here.
What's that one?
Oh, it's return.
Okay.
It's jungle time, baby.
Levitation.
What happens here?
What was that one?
Weakening curse explosives.
I have that already.
Now, let's be careful still.
This is how you explore the dark areas.
You just go with the drill.
I want to go into the Lukey layer again.
There's bound to be more hearts there.
Oh, wow.
You died quick.
Unless you were the one I already damaged from earlier.
Because I didn't change anything here.
This is the same damage as before.
Right.
Oh yeah, that is the guy I damaged earlier.
Because he was roaming in this place, remember?
I'm not in the Lukey layer yet.
He was just chilling.
You know, now I'm wondering.
Because the game doesn't simulate unless you close.
But sometimes these spiders dig massive holes.
You know?
And they usually do it when I'm nowhere near them.
So, maybe enemies are still like simulated, but liquids and stuff are not.
I can dig through anything now.
Oh, I remember this spot.
I remember this.
I think I went back because of the clouds, right?
Yeah, that's it.
Perfect timing.
You know, they're not actually that bad.
Like, my permanent shield is doing wonders here.
I just gotta be real careful.
Like, as soon as they bounce off my shield, I need to go for the shot.
I get a little staggered after that.
Uh-oh.
Guys?
Oh!
What?
Oh, twitchy.
I'm gonna make a little shooting hole.
Oh, shit.
Burn away the poison.
Shit, there's poison everywhere.
Get rid of that crap.
Okay, guys, come here.
Spiders?
Show yourself?
They're still healing.
Oh, shit.
Got him.
Look at all the poison below me.
Oh, no, it's those guys.
What are they doing here?
Fuck off.
Are you scared of me?
One of them is down, nice.
Uh-oh.
Kill that dude immediately.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Come here.
There we go.
They're not that bad.
It's okay.
Wait.
Teleportation.
I kind of wanted to do experiments with that.
But there's not enough of it, I think.
If anything, I would like to have a full bottle of it.
Where'd the other spider go?
I'm in deep water here.
Do not run into spaces you haven't been before.
So let's just clear a little path here.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, so we're back here now.
Perfect.
Come here.
Come here, damn it.
Come on.
There we go.
Down with you.
Man, one of the toughest enemies in the game.
They are just horrible to fight.
Oh, wait a minute.
He's blue.
Oh, now he's dead.
Okay, no, I thought he was frozen or something for a second.
Oh, maybe he was.
Freezing vapor.
Maybe that's the way to kill them.
Like, properly.
Just...
What the...
Hello?
What the fuck is this?
What is that place?
Oh, my God.
Something is invisible.
Oh, it's this thing.
Hello?
He shot some kind of bullshit.
Oh, it's dark in here, man.
It's like the Wizards then.
Sweet, what?
They have HP.
I'm curious to see what their attacks do to me.
But I don't want to get hit by it.
Wait, is this not staying lit?
After I explore?
Okay, it is, I think.
That's something, at least.
Oh, man, this is so wild.
I've discovered, like, four new areas today.
Is that a spider?
It is!
Oh, man.
Two of them, too.
Oh!
Gracias!
Oh, there's lava there.
That's so weird.
Oh, shit.
Gotta have an escape route.
The good news is the spiders seem to be weirdly indifferent to me, and they just sort of happen to go towards me sometimes.
I mean, they aggro on me, but it's not a, like, serious aggro.
It's just sort of weird.
Okay, one down.
Good stuff.
Nice!
Don't fuck with me!
Now, I haven't gotten a name for this place.
Uh, spiders come out of that.
I don't want to destroy it.
Oh, man, this is scary.
Oh!
Oh, no.
He was one of those teleport people.
You bastard!
This is probably a bad idea what I'm doing here.
Keep the lights going.
Destroy this thing.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
Whoa!
Kill him, kill him!
We need some proper blood in here.
Not that diamond blood shit.
I see you there.
Wait, why am I taking...
Okay, it's...
Water it?
Bro, where am...
Oh, another heart.
Yo, this is big.
Oh my god.
Kill him.
Damn, you have HP.
They are tangy.
Thank god I have a light on this, huh?
Wow, that is completely carrying me right now.
Imagine if I didn't.
This would have been a shit show.
I feel like I'm playing really well.
Oh, no.
Yeah, it's one of those guys.
We switch places.
Super scary.
No!
Fuck!
Wait, did he just turn someone else into a sheep?
What just happened there?
Don't hit me.
Fuck off.
That is scary.
Especially when you can't see shit in here.
Holy crap.
Because that's the roof here.
Okay, so that's the edge here.
And the entrance.
Oh, is this a sub-hemus?
Sub-fools.
Give me money.
Okay, so that comes in there.
Interesting.
Okay, so we have a little area...
in the looky layer.
And it's like...
it goes in...
I don't know, it likes...
maybe something like that.
Goes up.
Let's just do something like this for now.
We have to see how this area actually looks.
No name yet.
That I've seen.
But it reminds me...
of the magical temple.
And this is teleportation.
Careful with that.
But wait, now there's more looky layer.
It is so weird.
What's in here?
Not much.
Man, this place is scary.
I wonder what that spell is.
There you are.
Don't hit me with that, please.
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Do not do that.
No, don't even think about it.
One of these could be a polymorph.
And that is something that I hate.
Oh, shit.
At least I got him.
This guy has a lot of HP.
One of the more tanky ones.
Lava is scary.
Man, this is the roof.
Okay.
Seems good.
Let's slowly dig.
Got lava below me.
It's not.
Don't shoot me with that crap.
Yo, what is this area now?
What?
This is so fucked.
Ah!
He keeps teleporting me.
He's got to be dead now.
Man, fuck you.
There we go.
Okay.
Where am I?
Snowy depths?
No way.
No, no, no.
This is not snowy depths.
Wait.
It could be.
If this somehow connects without me knowing it?
No way.
No, no, no, no.
There's no way.
This is another region.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
We need blood.
The fuck is that?
Those are kind of blue...
Something following me.
I hate it.
Okay, yeah.
Does damage.
Huh?
Wait, he's immune.
I have been mindfucked this entire session.
And I love it.
It's the best.
It's so exciting.
Uh-oh.
I hear electric sparks.
Oh, it's you.
Are you going to leave me alone there?
Huh?
Why do I not get a name for this place?
Oh, this thing is still following me.
Okay, I made it a little safer.
Don't shoot me with that shit.
Snowy wasteland.
Wait.
I've seen that message before.
Snowy wasteland.
I'm going to dig up all the way up.
Same technique as last time.
Oh, look at this.
What?
This is wild.
And then the...
Okay.
I'm hearing explosions and very intriguing music.
Hold on, I need to take a bite out of my sandwich.
It's tuna.
Come on.
Shit.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Hello.
Can I somehow get rid of these fuckers?
Oh, no.
Don't follow me.
Leave me alone.
I'm scared of water because...
Uco stone.
I heard something on the right.
Fuck.
No, no, no, no, no.
Shit.
Man, it just...
Okay, it's not following me anymore, it seems.
Okay, it is.
Never mind.
Shit, shit, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
Up, up, up, up, up, up.
That's a worm.
Straight up, straight up, straight up.
Damn.
Oh, wait, they're sort of invisible to me.
I can't hit them.
Leavik.
What the fuck?
That thing spawns?
An eye.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I remember this.
I saw this before.
Guys, I'm in a bit of a trouble here.
Oh, not you.
Not you.
We're going all the way up.
All the way up.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Leave me alone.
Careful, don't hit any explosives.
Okay.
Oh, they're all immune?
Okay, whatever.
I'm leaving.
I see.
Okay, he's somehow still immune.
That's fair.
Leave!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Surely, they're not going to follow me in here.
And surely, I'm not putting myself in a bad spot going in here.
I'm just going to dig right, see what happens.
Oh, no, wait.
Actually, I should dig up.
I'm scared of digging up when I'm in such a tight spot here, though.
Because it may damage me, so I'm going to make a little room here first.
Shit.
Also, where exactly am I?
Hold on.
Ah, fuck.
I'm sorry, guys.
I just got a message.
I'm sorry.
God damn it.
I was panicking, okay?
It was a panicking moment.
Shit!
Oh, man.
I need to have like a warning on screen.
I need to write some kind of software that will show me like a blinking thing.
If I'm playing and the overlay is on.
It's the only way to fix this.
Sometimes you just forget in the heat of the moment.
Ah, shit.
I'm going straight up.
Fuck, I wonder how long that has been there.
What's up, my old friend?
We meet again.
Unfortunately, I don't have the means right now.
Could I just pass through maybe?
I swear to God.
I'm just passing through.
I need to go heal.
Then I'll be back for your ass.
Okay.
I must be close to ancient laboratory, I guess.
Man, remember the last time I had Jalkimisti sign down here while I was wielding one of these laser cutters?
Yeah, I remember too.
Not a good time.
I'm getting flashbacks to that right now.
Oh, freedom.
Yes.
Yes, dude.
Oh, dude, I know what I'm doing.
I know what I'm gonna do.
I'm
gonna...
There you go.
Look at that for a moment.